<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>Morgrem and Grimmsnarl Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Thanks for your patience on the latest updates! The Impidimp family has now been added to the rankings. These Dark/Fairy types sport high Attack stats and solid movesets to compete in Great and Ultra League. Morgrem has slightly higher stat product for Great League while Grimmsnarl is the only one that can reach Ultra League. Both have corebreaking potential, excelling against Ghost types and rival Dark types.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/grimmsnarl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spidops Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Spidops is on a mission and it's getting the green light! Bug types usually need a lot of help, but Spidops has a few things going for it—good bulk plus a solid moveset with Lunge, Rock Tomb, and its choice of Shadow Claw or Bug Bite. Its closest comparisons are Golisopod and Forretress. Though it lacks their better typings, it still looks to be competitive in Open Great League. It may succeed more in themed cups where it will have fewer direct threats.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/spidops/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top Performers Updated</title><description><![CDATA[Top Performers are now updated for Great League and Ultra League with the past month of training data. In Great League, Forretress and Scizor are gaining a stronger foothold, while in Ultra League, Chilling Water Florges is beginning to break out into the meta. Take a look for some team ideas and good luck during this GO Battle Weekend!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:31:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadow Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Two new Shadow Pokemon debut in raids during part one of the Halloween Event - Phantum and Yamask. Their evolutions, Trevenant and Cofagrigus, aren't currently top Ghost-type options, but interesting additions to the Shadow roster. Shadow Trevenant relishes the reduced energy cost of Seed Bomb and looks to be largely on par with the normal version. Meanwhile, Shadow Cofagrigus is at bit of a disadvantage with its slower moveset—not quite a nail in the coffin, but it'll have to wait for a faster Charged Attack option. Return looks intriguing for normal Cofagrigus and trainers brave enough to try it.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/trevenant_shadow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Halloween Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Spooky Season is upon us, and Halloween Cup returns in a few weeks! Powerful Poison, Steel, Ghost, and Dark types are in for a treat. With Nidoqueen returning as a top threat, look for rival Ground types like Golurk and Runerigus to make headway into the meta. Mandibuzz may also look to scare with its bulk, but there are strong alternatives in the Dark/Flying flock. Between them, legacy safe swaps like Shadow Drapion, Sableye, and Golisopod could see renewed play here as well. Happy haunting!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/halloween/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:46:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Remix Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Thanks for your patience on the Great League Remix rankings! The bans remained unannounced until the cup began, so it wasn't possible to prepare rankings ahead of time.<br><br>A selection of Bug and Normal types stand out in the rankings this time around, with Fire and Fighting types largely out of the picture. They will be tested against some of the best Great League Pokemon remaining, such as Diggersby, Clodsire, and Tinkaton. The meta looks wide open, so only time will tell how it will pare down. Best of luck!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/remix/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dipplin and Hydrapple Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Dipplin and Hydrapple share the same moveset, with Dipplin having the highest stat product of the evolutionary line. The apple doesn't fall far from the tree, however, as this difference in stat product isn't enough to elevate Dipplin in a meaningful way. These Pokemon will be waiting for their signature attacks to find more play!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/dipplin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:25:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Master Premier Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Master Premier's biggest players have grown even stronger since its last rotation. Chilling Water Florges, Shadow Claw Metagross, and Dragon Breath Gyarados are the top tier with few corebreakers between them. Other strong picks include Togekiss, Rhyperior, Goodra, and Primarina, but are likely to play second fiddle. The meta may depend on spicy corebreakers like Scizor, Skeledirge, or Chandelure to keep players on their toes.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/premier/10000/overall/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 15:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jungle Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Jungle Cup returns this season with a deep roster to choose from! Great League staples like Cradily and Corviknight should see plenty of play alongside less used picks like Altaria and Crustle. Crucial double weaknesses are present in this meta (especially Ice and Fire), so these may be important team building factors. It should be fun to see which new Pokemon emerge from the jungle!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/jungle/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top Performers Updated</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Top Performers page for all leagues with training data from the past month. Data is limited for Ultra League and Master League, so take those listings with a healthy dose of salt. In Great League, Ghost types continue to be a common element for top performing teams, typically paired with a Fighting-weak partner like Cradily, Bastiodon, or Furret. Take a look for some Pokemon and team ideas, and good luck as the season continues! ]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:37:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dudunsparce Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Dudunsparce has arrived as a more Attack-weighted alternative to Dunsparce. This difference generally puts it at a disadvantage and reduces its play in neutral matchups. With the exact same moveset as its pre-evolution, Dudunsparce lacks any distinguishing factors. However, it can reach Ultra League!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/dudunsparce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rankings and Editor Scores</title><description><![CDATA[The site's rankings now include "Editor Scores", personal ratings and notes for some individual Pokemon. These scores aim to highlight core meta Pokemon, correct ratings for Pokemon which may be under represented in the simulations, and provide additional commentary outside of the simulated results.<br><br>Editor scores will be expanded and updated across the three main leagues as the season progresses. I hope the results make the rankings more helpful!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fantasy Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Fantasy Cup returns in a few weeks, and the kingdom looks like it'll have quite a few shakeups. With significant changes to Dragons and a number of powerful new Fairies, Steel types like Galarian Stunfisk, Empoleon, and Corviknight look to have a major advantage. There are plenty of Pokemon with mixed movesets in the running, such as Turtonator, Togekiss, or Forretress. Azumarill is likely to remain core meta but faces more challenges this time around.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/fantasy/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadows and Team Builder Tweaks</title><description><![CDATA[A batch of new Shadows are releasing soon! All of them are promising PvP picks, including Altaria, Zweilous, and Claydol. Of the bunch, Zweilous and Hydreigon have the speed to take the most advantage of the Shadow boost.<br><br>In addition, I've made a few updates to the Team Builder to improve usability and results. Shadow Pokemon are now enabled by default, and follow the emphasis on meta picks so that the results highlight meta relevant Shadows. Suggested Alternatives also now use a more curated threats list, removing similar Pokemon from the list. For example, Shadow and non-Shadow versions of the same Pokemon won't be included in the six threats used to generated the Suggested Alternatives results.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 18:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flabébé Community Day Guide for PvP</title><description><![CDATA[Florges is learning Chilling Water this coming Community Day! It will be a strong contender in all three leagues, so don't miss out. Here's a deep dive on IV's to look for and Florges's prospects this season. Have fun!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/community-day/25-09-flabebe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 01:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>