<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Updated Great League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Top performers have been updated with a first look at the meta this season! The overall changes are small, but there are notable shifts just within the first week.<br><br>Diggersby and Morpeko top the individual performers, both with buffs this season. Annihilape and Primeape are also firmly in the running, with Annihilape scoring slightly ahead of Primeape. On top performing teams, there's a good amount of variety. Common elements include Normal types (Diggersby or Dunsparce), Water types (Feraligatr, Gastrodon, and Azumarill), and a resurgence in Grass (Serperior, Jumpluff, and a few Ferrothorn).<br><br>A few newcomers don't have enough data to support them yet, such as Bibarel, Starmie, and Thunder Fang Steelix. Time will tell if these Pokemon have a shot at a meta or anti-meta role. Stay tuned for more updates!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 16:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Little Holiday Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Little Holiday Cup returns in a few weeks, although note that Smeargle's eligibility is still tentative. (It was included and then later banned prior to the cup's previous release.)<br><br>Besides Smeargle, the cup's strongest contenders include Alolan Sandslash, Fire types like Alolan Marowak, Skeledirge, and Litwick, Pikachu Libre, and other odd picks like Miltank or Amaura. As always, Fast Attack pressure can be lethal in Little Cup, so watch out for Charm users like Wigglytuff and Alolan Ninetales, too.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/holiday/500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 23:37:27 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Updates for Dual Destiny</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The site has been updated for the current season, Dual Destiny! This season brings a few minor attack updates, including buffs to Thunder Shock, the Elemental Fangs, and the Elemental Punches.<br><br>Thunder Shock's increase in base power makes it equivalent to Poison Sting again. If you weren't seeing it enough already, this change should solidify Morpeko as a core meta Pokemon. Its ability to farm down opponents is now improved, especially after Attack boosts. Morpeko previously sat low in the rankings, but I've updated its Consistency score to better reflect how it's used in play.<br><br>Meanwhile, the Fang and Punch buffs only have minor impact. Few Pokemon can use the Fangs effectively, limited to Steelix, Mawile, and potentially Arctibax. Even then, their alternative attacks may be better. Alolan Sandslash, Diggersby, Goodra, Shadow Typhlosion, and Groudon all benefit from the Punch buffs and should see more play into this season.<br><br>Good luck with your early battles and see you for more updates!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:19:31 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Updated Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted training analysis for all three leagues and the final analysis for the season! The past month included several Great League cups, so note that the top performers may be skewed by some practice teams from Halloween, Remix, and Retro. Good luck the final week of the season and see you for the next one on December 1st!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Galarian Corsola and Cursola Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Galarian Corsola is debuting in the season finale event, and barring any prerelease changes, it looks like a monster for PvP. It pairs high bulk with strong moves in Astonish and Night Shade plus Power Gem for coverage, all three of which got buffed this past season.<br><br>This ghost demolishes the newly invigorated Annihilape and provides a solid answer to meta Poison types like Clodsire and Ariados. It does have to contend with prominent Normal and Dark types like Dunsparce, Drapion, and Mandibuzz, so it's not without its flaws. Similar to Bastiodon and Carbin, Galarian Corsola reaches its highest stat product at level 50, but high IV versions can be fielded near level 40.<br><br>Meanwhile, Cursola can reach higher CP than Corsola but is a true glass cannon. It lacks the stat product and moves to compete in any of the three leagues. It's ultimately unlikely to find a niche over other Ghosts.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/corsola_galarian/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 17:09:42 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Retro Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Sometimes retro things make a comeback, and that includes Retro Cup this November. Steel, Fairy, and Dark types are banned, which leaves a pretty wide pool remaining that should play pretty close to open Great League. However, the door is open for more Dragon, Ghost, Ice, and Psychic types to see play. Double Dragon may prove to be a popular strategy again since Dragon attacks are unresisted. Normal types should also play a key role as the only Ghost resistance in the meta. Check out the rankings for more details!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/retro/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 19:31:33 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mankey Community Day Guide for PvP</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The Mankey family is getting a big Community Day with Primeape and Annihilape both learning Rage Fist! Both should have play in PvP. Check out IV's to look for and tips for the upcoming event. Have fun!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/community-day/24-11-mankey/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 17:13:42 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Updated Great League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[With GO Battle Weekend beginning tomorrow, I've updated the Training Analysis page with top performers from the past few weeks of Great League practice. The Pokemon topping the charts are by and large established meta at this point, although Morpeko and even Pangoro put up some good recent numbers. Clodsire dominates the top performing teams, most often partnered with a Water type such as Feraligatr, Azumarill, or Gastrodon. Good luck in your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 19:16:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Performance Improvements</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've launched performance improvements to the Rankings page which should now be faster and more lightweight. If you notice any freezing, lag, or slowdown, you can also enable a new Performance Mode option from the Settings page, which further improves CPU performance on the Rankings page.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:49 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Willpower Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Willpower Cup returns featuring Dark, Psychic, and Fighting-type Pokemon. Gardevoir is banned, but other Fairies sneak through, including Hatterene and Galarian Rapidash. With few resistances, Charm could be a running theme, but Poison Jab and Poison Sting are strong enough to overcome it. Some niche Pokemon like Claydol should also see play. Have fun!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/willpower/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 03:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Morpeko Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Morpeko will debut as the first Pokemon to change forms mid-battle! This form change occurs whenever it uses a Charged Attack. Depending on its form, its powerful signature move, Aura Wheel, is either an Electric-type or Dark-type attack.<br><br>Morpeko fits the mold of other glassy Electric types like Magnezone, Togedemaru, and Luxray, equipped with a bait move and a powerful nuke. It's likely to remain spice but should be fun to experiment with. We'll see if the form change mechanic comes to other Pokemon in the future!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/morpeko_full_belly/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 16:21:18 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Expanded Multi-Battle and Matrix Battle Options</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The groups you set for Multi-Battle and Matrix Battle now feature the same simulation options as Single Battle, such as starting HP, starting energy, and stat modifiers. You can use these options to explore advanced scenarios, such as which Pokemon can beat Clodsire after switching in, or breakpoints between different IV spreads when you have an Attack buff. Enjoy tinkering around!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Updated Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated top performers data for all three leagues from training so far this season. Note that Ultra and Master League training data is limited, so your mileage may vary with the top performing teams!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 00:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Halloween Cup and Great League Remix Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted initial rankings for Halloween Cup and Great League Remix! Halloween Cup has fewer dramatic changes, with Pokemon like Mandibuzz, Azumarill, and Drapion still taking the spotlight. Clodsire is in the mix now too, so expect it to shape the meta going forward.<br><br>Great League Remix now bans top picks from the current season instead of the previous season. However, expect some of those previous season mainstays to make an appearance! Whiscash is one of the strongest Water types left standing, while Bastiodon, Registeel, and potentially even Lanturn are also in play.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/halloween/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:21:26 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Shadow Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[A new batch of Shadow Pokemon are debuting! The Mankey family is the most noteworthy with a Community Day coming later this month. Shadow Primeape improves to be a viable contender alongside Machamp and Pangoro, and it may want to consider the legacy move Cross Chop. Annihilape will have to wait for future moves to be relevant again, but its Shadow version is well worth obtaining during the event! Meanwhile, Heatran looks like a slight improvement over the non-Shadow and is a rare chance to obtain one for Great League. Obstagoon, Escavalier, and Scolipede are likewise worth grabbing in case of future move changes.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/primeape_shadow/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 17:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Leavanny Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Sewaddle Community Day this Saturday brings Shadow Claw to Leavanny! It'll be a spicy pick that may even see some themed cup play thanks to Leaf Blade and X-Scissor, both powerful 35-energy attacks. It won't stick around the battlefield for a long time, but it'll be a fun one!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/leavanny/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:56:55 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>
