<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>Gamemaster Editor [Beta]</title><description><![CDATA[I've launched a new feature in beta called the Gamemaster Editor, which allows you to edit Pokemon and move entries for your simulations. You can use this feature to preview upcoming move changes, speculate on new moves, or Pokemon which don't exist in the game data yet.<br><br>Note that this feature is for advanced users, and may change the simulation results or even break them. Check out the link for more details on how the Gamemaster Editor impacts the site and how to use it!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/gm-editor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[With GO Battle Weekend approaching, I've updated the Great League top performers with the past few weeks of training data. Bug types are out in force this round, including Shadow Scizor, Fortress, and Golisopod on a number of top teams. Staple generalists like Cradily, Kanto Marowak, and Lapras continue to put up good numbers as the meta evolves. Keep an eye out for Fire types looking to prey on the latest shifts.<br><br>This update doesn't include data for Shadow Giratina Altered yet, so the meta may see even more distribution in its last few weeks. If you're looking to give Giratina a try, it can substitute for Dusclops or Galarian Corsola on the top performing teams. Good luck this weekend!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 19:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadow Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[A long awaited specter finally arrives in Great League—Altered Giratina! With bulky stats similar to Altaria, excellent Ghost/Dragon typing, and solid moves, it's easy to envision that Altered Giratina will carve a core spot in the metagame. As the Shadow version, it should be a fantastic generalist with either Ghost or Dragon offenses. That decision may come down to your team or your playstyle.<br><br>Giratina isn't the only potent Shadow debuting during the upcoming event. Shadow Talonflame and Shadow Charjabug are also great picks to watch out for. Talonflame in particular possesses terrifying Fast Attack pressure which it can ramp up if it builds into Flame Charge.<br><br>Note that these new Shadow Pokemon are not eligible for the Play! Pokemon Worlds Championship.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/giratina_altered_shadow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultra League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Ultra League top performers with analysis from the past month of training. There appears to be a lot of experimentation among the top teams even as Bellibolt solidifies itself as a core meta threat. Water types don't appear to be deterred, with Feraligatr, Lapras, and Tentacruel making up some of the top performing picks. Fairy is another successful piece, represented by Florges, Galarian Weezing, or Tinkaton for those with the resources. Good luck in this Ultra week!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/2500/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 20:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frosmoth Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Frosmoth makes its debut as an egg exclusive Pokemon. With Ice/Bug typing and glass cannon stats, it has a lot going against it. Its moveset is serviceable with Powder Snow plus Icy Wind, but it needs a lot more help to see competitive play. Talonflame is eager for the easy meal!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/frosmoth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CMP Chart Page</title><description><![CDATA[I've added a new page which shows the range of possible Attack stats for Pokemon in a format. You can examine which Pokemon species have overlapping Attack stats and which CMP ties are most likely to be IV dependent. The list can be customized if you want to explore a different set of Pokemon. Happy studying!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/attack-cmp-chart/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Great League top performers with a sampling of teams and Pokemon from recent training. While this sample is small, it highlights some successful experimentation with Pokemon like Pangoro, Dragalge, and Galarian Moltres. Good luck in your battles and keep up the practice!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toedscruel Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Toedscruel debuts as a Grass/Ground type with the same bulk as its toxic lookalike. With a solid moveset, it can pair Mud Slap with Seed Bomb, Earth Power, Wrap, or Acid Spray. Wrap in particular gives it similar play to Gastrodon, plus a guaranteed Defense drop to bolster its Fast Attack pressure.<br><br>Unlike Gastrodon, Toedscruel's typing gives it more weaknesses to juggle. Its triple resistance to Electric and single resistance to Ground are offset by a double weakness to Ice and single weaknesses to Fire, Flying, and Bug. This profile limits Toedscruel as a Mud Slapper generalist, so it must seek out top targets like Dedenne, Marowak, or Clodsire to counter. Even with Seed Bomb, it struggles against Water types, which often pack Ice coverage. It should see play in themed cups and perhaps it'll find an anti-meta role too!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/toedscruel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aegislash Update</title><description><![CDATA[After a crazy debut, the dust has settled on Aegislash! The simulations have now been updated to implement Aegislash's forme change mechanic. Aegislash begins in its bulky Shield forme and transforms into its glass cannon Sword form before it launches any Charged Attack. It reverts to its Shield forme when it uses a Protect Shield or swaps out.<br><br>While in Shield forme, Aegislash's Fast Attack is overridden to have 0 base power and generate 6 energy per use. While in Blade forme, Aegislash's effective level is reduced in Great and Ultra League in an attempt to keep its new CP under the league caps.<br><br>Aegislash is most effective when it minimizes its time in Blade forme. Generally, Aegislash should seek to build up to 100 energy before throwing. It should also absorb hits while in Shield forme to save shields for its Blade forme. On the flip side, opponents should avoid throwing energy into Aegislash's Shield forme and wait until it's vulnerable in its Blade forme. Fast Attack pressure is key to countering Aegislash, which is especially vulnerable to poor Charged Attack timing.<br><br>I'll continue to watch for more details on Aegislash's mechanics and provide QOL updates to help analyze this crazy new Pokemon. Thanks for your patience!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/aegislash_shield/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title/><description><![CDATA[Quaquaval will be receiving Aqua Step as a regular addition to its movepool, and Hydro Cannon as an exclusive move during its upcoming Community Day! Aqua Step boosts its Attack by one stage, but it's overshadowed by the sheer power of Hydro Cannon.<br><br>While Quaquaval has great Charged Attack options, it wishes for the days of peak Wing Attack. It won't see much play until it finds better energy generation in a future update. In the meantime, grab some for the collection and have fun!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/quaquaval/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:27:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Team Builder Update</title><description><![CDATA[The Team Builder now prioritizes showing meta relevant Pokemon in its threats and suggested alternatives. This should help provide better suggestions and threats which you are more likely to encounter (sorry, Fletchinder).You can disable this feature in the advanced settings if you want to explore more spice picks or find off-meta corebreakers. Have fun!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/team-builder/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Master League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[Master League is returning, and it's undergoing a monumental shakeup with the arrival of the Crowned forms of Zacian and Zamazenta. Top performing teams highlight Crowned Zacian + Origin Palkia as one of the most common and successful cores. Kyurem (both Black and White) still appears to remain a major player, but Dusk Mane Necrozma is on a downturn, dropping significantly in team rating and usage.<br><br>"If you can't beat 'em, join 'em" has never been more true for Master League. However, a few Pokemon are holding on for an anti-meta role. Rhyperior and Landorus still land among the top performing teams despite their weaknesses, and Dawn Wings Necrozma stands out with solid matchups against the core meta. With Solgaleo now more widely available, time will tell if it has a role to play as well.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/10000/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 17:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Update to Default IV's</title><description><![CDATA[The rankings and default simulations don't use rank 1 IV's, but lower ranked IV combinations which are intended to represent an average version of the Pokemon. The default IV's were previously around ranks 150-300 depending on the Pokemon and followed rules which were difficult to explain. In response to survey feedback, I've tweaked the default IV's with the following changes.<br><br>- Default IV's now use the best ranked IV combination with an IV floor of 4. Default IV's are now around ranks 50-150, but still keep that distinct Attack weight for the sake of comparison.<br>- In cases where the above doesn't reach the CP limit, Pokemon will use the best ranked Lucky IV combination (floor of 12).<br>- Overall, default IV's should better represent competitive play.<br><br>You may notice some slight shifts in the rankings due to these changes, as the default IV change may allow some Pokemon to reach breakpoints or bulkpoints which the previous IV's didn't.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:30:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultra League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[While training data for Ultra League has only a small sample, I've posted the results so far and updated the default training teams to reflect the new Bellibolt meta. This smiley chunkster demands counterplay from picks like Gastrodon, Virizion, and Guzzlord. Zygarde Complete also looks like the complete package if you have the option. Best of luck in your practice and thanks for any training you contribute!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/2500/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisuian Zoroark Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisuian Zoroark is a unique Ghost/Normal typing, which makes it the only Pokemon to resist both Ghost and Fighting attacks. However, as a Haunter-like glass cannon, Hisuian Zoroark can't take much damage of any kind! Its movepool gives it some play as a spice pick, with access to Shadow Claw, Foul Play, and Shadow Ball for a mix of Fast Attack pressure, speed, and nuke potential. Be prepared for some quick battles!<br><br>]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/zoroark_hisuian/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 16:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>