<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated Top Performers with a first look at Great League this season. As the meta continues to evolve, top performing teams highlight several newcomers, including Corviknight, Empoleon, and Togekiss, and a strengthening role for Stunfisk against them. Ghost is another successful group in the early running, often paired with Cradily or Gastrodon. While Primeape usage is trending up, its performance has plummeted. Clodsire is another struggling member of the old guard.<br><br>The meta is changing fast with lots of new picks to explore, so time will tell which will come out on top in the early season!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 20:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Season of Transformation Updates</title><description><![CDATA[The site has been updated for Season of Transformation! There are some differences between the final move values and the ones speculated on the preview site, so the rankings have been updated to reflect these. Look forward to Summer Cup rankings soon and further updates as we roll into the new season. Have fun!<br><br>]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookidee Community Day Guide for PvP</title><description><![CDATA[Corviknight has hovered on the edge of the PvP meta, but may finally have its chance to swoop in. It's getting a crucial speed buff with its exclusive attack, Air Cutter. Will it be enough to push Corviknight into core relevance? Let's look ahead to the move updates next season to get a bird's-eye view on Corviknight's prospects.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/community-day/25-08-rookidee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:55:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[With one last week in the season, I've updated Great League top performers with the past few weeks of training data. Shadow Giratina makes a peek in this data but it's still too early to draw any conclusions. Cradily has a firm stake in the top performing teams. Water and Ghost continue to be prominent typings, although an increase in Dark (specifically, Galarian Moltres) doesn't bode well for some of the Ghosts. Good luck the rest of the season and see you for the next one! Expect some major shakeups!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dondozo Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Dondozo is a pure Water type which is making its debut in raids. Its high base HP gives it a stat product similar to Lapras, but its Fast Attack options in Water Gun and Waterfall currently limit its effectiveness. It has future potential, so look to catch one for your collection!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/dondozo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:55:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Season Preview</title><description><![CDATA[I've posted a preview version of the site which includes moves, movesets, and rankings with the announced changes. Since many energy values can't be confirmed until the new season begins, this preview is highly speculative. It should serve as a potential reference, but avoid investing in any Pokemon until the move updates are confirmed. Happy studying!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/new-season-2026/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternatus Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Eternatus makes its massive debut, and it's going to take massive dedication to power it up. For Master League players, Eternatus can firmly hold its own among the legendary powerhouses. Its Poison subtyping is largely a footnote compared to its huge stat product and its powerful signature move, Dynamax Cannon. Like other Dragons, it will struggle against Zacian and Zamazenta, but it should have no trouble finding play especially as we look forward to next season.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gamemaster Editor [Beta]</title><description><![CDATA[I've launched a new feature in beta called the Gamemaster Editor, which allows you to edit Pokemon and move entries for your simulations. You can use this feature to preview upcoming move changes, speculate on new moves, or Pokemon which don't exist in the game data yet.<br><br>Note that this feature is for advanced users, and may change the simulation results or even break them. Check out the link for more details on how the Gamemaster Editor impacts the site and how to use it!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/gm-editor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[With GO Battle Weekend approaching, I've updated the Great League top performers with the past few weeks of training data. Bug types are out in force this round, including Shadow Scizor, Fortress, and Golisopod on a number of top teams. Staple generalists like Cradily, Kanto Marowak, and Lapras continue to put up good numbers as the meta evolves. Keep an eye out for Fire types looking to prey on the latest shifts.<br><br>This update doesn't include data for Shadow Giratina Altered yet, so the meta may see even more distribution in its last few weeks. If you're looking to give Giratina a try, it can substitute for Dusclops or Galarian Corsola on the top performing teams. Good luck this weekend!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 19:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadow Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[A long awaited specter finally arrives in Great League—Altered Giratina! With bulky stats similar to Altaria, excellent Ghost/Dragon typing, and solid moves, it's easy to envision that Altered Giratina will carve a core spot in the metagame. As the Shadow version, it should be a fantastic generalist with either Ghost or Dragon offenses. That decision may come down to your team or your playstyle.<br><br>Giratina isn't the only potent Shadow debuting during the upcoming event. Shadow Talonflame and Shadow Charjabug are also great picks to watch out for. Talonflame in particular possesses terrifying Fast Attack pressure which it can ramp up if it builds into Flame Charge.<br><br>Note that these new Shadow Pokemon are not eligible for the Play! Pokemon Worlds Championship.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/giratina_altered_shadow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultra League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Ultra League top performers with analysis from the past month of training. There appears to be a lot of experimentation among the top teams even as Bellibolt solidifies itself as a core meta threat. Water types don't appear to be deterred, with Feraligatr, Lapras, and Tentacruel making up some of the top performing picks. Fairy is another successful piece, represented by Florges, Galarian Weezing, or Tinkaton for those with the resources. Good luck in this Ultra week!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/2500/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 20:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frosmoth Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Frosmoth makes its debut as an egg exclusive Pokemon. With Ice/Bug typing and glass cannon stats, it has a lot going against it. Its moveset is serviceable with Powder Snow plus Icy Wind, but it needs a lot more help to see competitive play. Talonflame is eager for the easy meal!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/frosmoth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CMP Chart Page</title><description><![CDATA[I've added a new page which shows the range of possible Attack stats for Pokemon in a format. You can examine which Pokemon species have overlapping Attack stats and which CMP ties are most likely to be IV dependent. The list can be customized if you want to explore a different set of Pokemon. Happy studying!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/attack-cmp-chart/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Great League top performers with a sampling of teams and Pokemon from recent training. While this sample is small, it highlights some successful experimentation with Pokemon like Pangoro, Dragalge, and Galarian Moltres. Good luck in your battles and keep up the practice!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toedscruel Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Toedscruel debuts as a Grass/Ground type with the same bulk as its toxic lookalike. With a solid moveset, it can pair Mud Slap with Seed Bomb, Earth Power, Wrap, or Acid Spray. Wrap in particular gives it similar play to Gastrodon, plus a guaranteed Defense drop to bolster its Fast Attack pressure.<br><br>Unlike Gastrodon, Toedscruel's typing gives it more weaknesses to juggle. Its triple resistance to Electric and single resistance to Ground are offset by a double weakness to Ice and single weaknesses to Fire, Flying, and Bug. This profile limits Toedscruel as a Mud Slapper generalist, so it must seek out top targets like Dedenne, Marowak, or Clodsire to counter. Even with Seed Bomb, it struggles against Water types, which often pack Ice coverage. It should see play in themed cups and perhaps it'll find an anti-meta role too!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/toedscruel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>