<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Hisuian Zoroark Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisuian Zoroark is a unique Ghost/Normal typing, which makes it the only Pokemon to resist both Ghost and Fighting attacks. However, as a Haunter-like glass cannon, Hisuian Zoroark can't take much damage of any kind! Its movepool gives it some play as a spice pick, with access to Shadow Claw, Foul Play, and Shadow Ball for a mix of Fast Attack pressure, speed, and nuke potential. Be prepared for some quick battles!<br><br>]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/zoroark_hisuian/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 16:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisui Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisui Cup will be returning in a few weeks, and it should play a bit different this time around but with some usual suspects crowding the scene. Drapion, Gliscor, and Gastrodon form a hard triangle against which corebreakers like Drifblim, Vespiquen, and Empoleon may find play. Add Spiritomb into the mix, and you have a subset of flexible Pokemon which only sport one weakness each. As usual, themed cups are about finding hidden opportunities in a limited meta, so we'll see which gems are out there!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/hisui/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 23:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>PvPoke.com Feedback Survey</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted a feedback survey to help gather information on which areas of the website you'd like to see improve and which new features you'd most be interested in. I'll be using this feedback to address any changes requested by the community and plan site updates over the next few months. Thanks in advance and thanks for your support!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://forms.gle/ZPUr1Vz45AUXpbis7</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:41:31 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated Great League training analysis from the first leg of the season, including top Pokemon and teams which players have practiced.<br><br>The data highlights opportunities for Pokemon like Shadow Gligar, Shadow Typhlosion, and the Bug/Water types of Araquanid and Golisopod to make headway into the meta. Shadow Scizor and Dedenne are also putting up strong individual performances, backed by early tournament results.<br><br>A few curious patterns appear on top performing teams. Normal types such as DIggersby, Furret, and Dunsparce are a common successful element, paired with a Fire type like Talonflame or Shadow Typhlosion. This is a time of rapid change as the meta seeks to resolve itself, so your mileage may vary. Best of luck as we head further into the season!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 23:09:31 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kommo-o Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[This upcoming Community Day, Kommo-o will receive its signature move, Clanging Scales. As of now, Clanging Scales is the highest damage-per-energy attack in the game, with 120 base power at the cost of 45 energy and a 1-stage Defense drop. However, Kommo-o faces problems if it wants to put Clanging Scales into practice.<br><br>Kommo-o isn't quite a glass cannon, but has below average stat product. Energy generation with Dragon Tail can be cumbersome, so Kommo-o and similar Dragon types perform best with 35-energy attacks like Dragon Claw or Aqua Tail. If Kommo-o wants to use Clanging Scales, it must sacrifice either pacing or coverage. By dropping Dragon Claw, Kommo-o's impressive attacks are simply outpaced. By dropping Close Combat, Kommo-o loses the ability to hit back at Steel. Brick Break is a middle ground, but doesn't appear fast or strong enough to solve the problem.<br><br>Kommo-o seems to perform best in Ultra League where it has more bulk to work with and it can reach its powerful attacks more reliably. Despite Clanging Scales tipping the scales on attack power, Kommo-o may need to wait for better energy generation to actually make some noise in the metagame. That said, make sure to take advantage of the event to prepare one for your collection!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/kommo_o/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:07:32 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Performance Improvements</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've pushed various performance improvements including battle and interface optimizations:<br><br>- Battle simulations should be about 25% faster, with more noticeable improvement in bulk simulations (such as the Team Builder or Custom Rankings)<br>- The Pokemon Select dropdown now only displays Pokemon near the current selection rather than the full Pokedex.<br>- The above should help the "Add Pokemon" window on Team Builder or Matrix Battle appear immediately rather than after a delay.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 15:13:53 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Summer Cup (UL) Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Summer Cup is returning, this time in Ultra League. It features prominent Water, Electric, and Grass types with a handful of Fire, Normal, and Bugs clawing for relevancy. As usual in these limited formats, Pokemon which can break the mold of their type typically prove the strongest. Here, this includes Cradily, Victreebel, Tentracruel, Lapras, Jellicent, and Golisopod. This cup may be resource demanding if you haven't built the requisite Pokemon yet, so now may be a good opportunity to expand your Ultra League roster. Good luck and enjoy the sun!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/summer/2500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:12:51 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Updated Great League Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The first week of the season well underway, and I've updated the Great League rankings with new weightings based on Pokemon usage so far. This update increases the scoring influence of popular Pokemon like Dedenne, Jellicent, and Talonflame while it decreases the scoring influence of Pokemon that have fallen off from last season, such as Malamar, Shadow Drapion, and Claydol.<br><br>As a whole, the meta is poised to resist the swarming Bug buffs. This has resulted in an early and widely predicted drop among most of Bug Bite and Fury Cutter users. Forretress, Golisopod, and Shadow Scizor appear to hold strong thanks to their advantageous typings. Other early fallers include Corviknight, who must contend with Talonflame and surging Electrics, and Tinkaton, whose Dark targets are vanishing and whose Steel typing is becoming more of a liability.<br><br>Early risers with opportunity in the forming meta include Diggersby, Kanto Marowak, and Gligar. These Ground types serve as vital checks to Dedenne and pack enough bulk and flexibility to soften their bad matchups.<br><br>NAIC is going to be a hotly contested tournament where all of the big meta changes will clash at the forefront. Given the tough dynamics of rising Pokemon like Dedenne, Jellicent, Talonflame, and Clodsire, success may hinge on finding the flexible safe swaps and corebreakers that can operate between them. Good luck in the early season and stay tuned for more updates!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:19:03 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Updated for Delightful Days</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The site and sims are updated for the newest season! If you've seen the preview site over the past week, the final numbers are just about the same as expected. This update include major buffs to Bug, Steel, and Poison types, which should introduce a number of viable picks into the metagame. Good luck through the early season and stay tuned for more site updates!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:00:34 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Delightful Days Preview</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[A preview for next season is now available! These are initial rankings and are subject to change depending on final attack values when the season launches. Delightful Days has the makings of a major shakeup with buffs to Bug-type attacks such as Bug Bite and Fury Cutter. Malamar's supremacy in the meta is about to be flipped on its head, with Golisopod becoming even stronger and picks like Forretress and Araquanid eying the spotlight.<br><br>There are a lot of angles to examine the new meta, so good luck with your research! I'll continue to refine the rankings leading up to the season's start on June 3rd, when we'll have a clear idea of updated attack stats. See you then!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/delightful-days/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:56:41 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Catch Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Anything goes in Catch Cup where you can battle with any Great League Pokemon you've caught this season. This should play like open Great League for the most part, but the availability of some staple picks (especially Shadows) may affect the metagame. Shadow Jumpluff, for example, has had a recent dominating stretch but may be benched for this cup.<br><br>A few thrifty and popular picks include Furret, Feraligatr, Skeledirge, and Thievul. Good luck during this GO Battle Week!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/catch/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:49:23 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Urshifu Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Kubfu will be able to evolve into Urshifu next week with the option of two styles, Rapid Strike (Fighting/Water) and Single Strike (Fighting/Dark). While Urshifu can fit into the lower leagues, it's best suited for Master League - although as we'll get to below, it may only have a short window in the metagame.<br><br>Single Strike Urshifu is currently the better of the two with access to Sucker Punch, while Rapid Strike has nerfed Counter. Single Strike's Dark typing is also more appealing than Water in the current Master League meta. Urshifu's stats and attacks fall short of top tier legendaries like Origin Palkia, Black/White Kyurem, and Necrozma, so it's likely to fill more of an anti-meta or corebreaking role.<br><br>However, Urshifu has to contend with the upcoming release of Crowned Zacian and Zamazenta, which look to shatter Master League as we know it. Both will significantly reduce its viability, ultimately making Urshifu a poor long term investment for PvP.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/urshifu_single_strike/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:30:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Retro Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Apologies for the delay! Initial rankings and resources are now posted for Retro Cup. Similar to the Remix we just saw, Retro Cup tosses out the biggest answers to Ghost and Dragon, leaving these offensive types to wreak havoc. Expect plenty of double-Ghost or double-Dragon lines in this format! Bulky Pokemon like Jumpluff and Lapras should provide anchors for other team building schemes.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/retro/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kingambit and New Shadow Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Kingambit and new Shadow Pokemon make their upcoming debuts. Kingambit is the final evolution of Bisharp and a Dark/Steel glass cannon. It's a spice pick for the lower leagues, but keep an eye on Master League and Master Premier where it has some corebreaker potential against Steel + Fairy teams. It will need to wait for its signature move or potential move updates to reach its full potential.<br><br>Shadow Malamar commands the most attention of the new batch. As a core meta Pokemon already, Shadow Malamar makes for an exciting alternative. It's well-suited for the Shadow role thanks to its Fast Attack pressure and spammy Charged Attacks. Aurorus is another interesting choice that will likely see play in themed cups. In Master League, Shadow Dialga carries big name recognition but is outclassed by the Origin form. Note that Shadow Dialga doesn't have the strict IV requirements of its non-Shadow counterpart - it will generally always deal and take 5 Dragon Breath damage in the mirror matchup.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/kingambit/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:32:12 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Team Builder and Bug Fixes</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've made the following site updates and fixes:<br><br>- Fixed an issue where using the "Custom Threats" option of the Team Builder would sometimes return unexpected results for suggested alternatives.<br>- Fixed an issue where the "Custom Alternatives" option of the Team Builder would use default movesets instead of the movesets provided.<br>- Fixed an issue where closing the Pokebox feature would prevent it from opening again.<br>- Play! Pokemon Championship format is now listed in the Team Builder and Multi-Battle.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>
