<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>Flamigo Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Flamigo makes its debut as a Flying/Fighting type with good future potential in PvP! This feathered friend is a glass cannon with access to strong attacks like Upper Hand and Brave Bird. Its Fast Attack options are serviceable in Double Kick and Wing Attack, but future access to Peck would elevate it to a true contender. Keep an eye out for this one!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/flamigo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:13:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top Performers Updated</title><description><![CDATA[The Top Performers page has been updated with training data collected since the start of the season for all three leagues. In Great League, Normal types like Furret and Wigglytuff prominently feature on top teams. A variety of Water types also continue the typing's dominance, including Jellicent and Empoleon. Spicier picks like Pangoro, Gourgeist, and Morpeko appear to have some opportunity against the current metagame, but they're not without risk. Good luck as the season progresses!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ninetales Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Vulpix's upcoming Community Day features both its Kanto and Alolan variants, receiving Energy Ball and Chilling Water, respectively. Both Ninetales are solid PvP options you'll want to catch if you don't have them in your collection already.<br><br>Chilling Water is a sidegrade for Alolan Ninetales, if not a slight improvement over Dazzling Gleam. It gives Alolan Ninetales coverage against Fire and Rock-type counters, plus more technical play across the board. The sims don't always use Chilling Water effectively, so it could prove better in practice than on paper. The downside of this moveset is it's fully resisted by Water types. This hasn't hindered previous meta picks, though, like Feraligatr or Lapras.<br><br>Kanto Ninetales has yet to find a secondary attack that unanimously displaces Overheat, and Energy Ball is unlikely to cross that hurdle. Energy Ball is a OHKO against Gastrodon and, of course, more effective into Water types than Overheat. Everywhere else, Overheat's sheer power is hard to give up. The addition of Energy Ball may improve Kanto Ninetales in GO Battle League, even for those that don't run it, but its prospects in tournament play are less optimistic.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/ninetales_alolan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:58:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Update</title><description><![CDATA[I live in Minneapolis. If you don’t know what’s happening right now in the United States, this is my alarm for anyone who will listen.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/development/personal-update-1-26-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadow Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[A batch of new Shadow Pokemon are debuting, including the Kalos starters! Greninja is the most exciting of the bunch, with the fastest Hydro Cannon in the game and now also the strongest. Night Slash, which lacks in raw damage, will benefit from the extra power as well. All in all, Shadow Greninja should be a general upgrade over the normal version. Time will tell if it has just enough bulk to compete! ]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/greninja_shadow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:22:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Sorry for the delay! Rankings are now available for Master and Ultra Premier Cup. Both should tread familiar territory. Master Premier welcomes Cetitan and Dragon Breath Tyranitar into the fold, while Gholdengo looks to surf to new heights. Ice types must contend with Metagross, which is more powerful than ever.<br><br>Ultra Premier only removes a handful of meta players like Virizion, Cobalion, and Giratina, so Ultra League players should feel right at home here. Some underused picks have a chance to shine, such as Forretress, Oranguru, or Ampharos.<br><br>Good luck in your battles!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/premier/10000/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kilowattrel Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Kilowattrel is an Electric/Flying type comparable to Zapdos in most respects, but also worse in most respects. It's even glassier and its cheapest attack, Aerial Ace, is a considerable downgrade from Drill Peck. If you don't have access to a Great League Zapdos, Kilowattrel can fill in for that spice role. Look to grab one just in case!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/kilowattrel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Retro Cup returns next week, and it should look similar to its previous runs. Without Dark, Fairy, or Steel types, Dragon and Psychic are the dominating offensive types. Anticipate teams to double up on these unresisted attackers. Ghost is another potent type, but is countered by key Normal types, including Oranguru, Furret, and Lickilicky. An anti-meta type to look into is Bug, with Pokemon like Golisopod, Crustle, and Araquanid providing counterplay to Psychic (Oranguru in particular).]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/retro/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blacepholon Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Blacepholon is lighting up the new year with its exclusive move, Mind Blown. At 35 energy and 90 base power, this Fire-type Attack is one of the most efficient in the game, but comes with a steep 4 stage debuff to Blacepholon's Defense. Blacepholon already an extreme glass cannon - even glassier than Haunter - so it has to hope that back-to-back attacks are enough to KO. It's a spicy addition to the Fire/Ghost spectrum, so enjoy it's short-lived time on the field!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/blacephalon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coalossal and Sunshine Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Sunshine Cup will kick off in the new year, featuring Normal, Grass, Fire, and Ground types. New among them will be Coalossal, a bulky Rock/Fire Pokemon comparable to Magcargo. It lacks Incinerate but sports even more bulk. While it it's unlikely to contend much in the open leagues, it does have a place in themed cups like this one. Happy holidays and new year's!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/sunshine/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:43:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Holiday Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[A lot has changed since Holiday Cup: Great League Edition last saw the GBL rotation in 2023. Normal types like Lickilicky, Dunsparce, and Furret stand out as versatile centerpieces, which must seek to avoid Annihilape and the format's various Steel types. Protecting them are dangerous Fire types including Talonflame and Skeledirge. There yet remain ghosts of Christmas past, as Sableye and Alolan Marowak are in strong contention. This cup is likely to be top-heavy, but there is a deep roster for corebreaking opportunities.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/holiday/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scroll Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Scroll Cup is returning, featuring Fighting, Water, and Dark-type Pokemon. This should remain a small meta with Gastrodon, Azumarill, and Dark/Flying types taking center stage. That said, recent changes give more viability to a few members of the cup. These include Kingdra, Sableye, Murkrow, Zweilous, Guzzlord, Jellicent, and more. Good luck in the early season!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/scroll/1500/overall</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 21:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precious Paths Update</title><description><![CDATA[The site is now updated for the latest season, Precious Paths! If you've checked the preview over the past week, the final attack values match what was expected. Keep an eye out for ranking updates as the season progresses and as the new meta game takes shape, with updated editor's scores and meta group selections. Enjoy the new season!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toucannon Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Toucannon is receiving Beak Blast this Community Day, and it's a big improvement for the plucky bird. Beak Blast has comparable numbers to Brave Bird, but instead of debuffing the attacker, it provides a guaranteed Attack drop on the opponent. This gives Toucannon similar prospects to Pidgeot, Dodrio, and other Pokemon with mono-Flying offenses, if perhaps a bit better. These Pokemon don't typically see much competitive action but are viable for GO Battle League and themed cup play.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/toucannon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precious Paths Preview Page</title><description><![CDATA[A preview version of the site is now available for Precious Paths, including all move updates for next season! Note that some of these are speculative as energy values won't be known until the season starts. Take a look and happy studying!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/precious-paths/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>