<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Master Premier and Tapu Bulu Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Rankings are now available for Master Premier Cup, which returns in a few weeks! It will feature several Pokemon new to the format, including Annihilape, Feraligatr, Skeledirge, and Golisopod. While Dragonite, Gyarados, and Fairies should continue to define the meta, these new picks will look at add some twists and corebreakers. Good luck preparing!<br><br>In regular Master League, Tapu Bulu is debuting with its exclusive move, Nature's Madness. Tapu Bulu has higher stat product compared to some of its companions, and its typing gives it a potential niche against both Dragon types and Kyogre. Unfortunately, its struggles against Dialga and Ho-oh may limit it in the current meta.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/premier/10000/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:38:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jungle Cup Training</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Jungle Cup is now available on the site's Train feature. You can use it to practice your teams or experiment with new Pokemon. Good luck preparing your Vigoroth counters! Training Analysis for Jungle Cup may be available next week if there's enough data.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:41:41 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great and Ultra League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The Great and Ultra League top performers are now updated with training data from the season so far. In the Great League, Dragon types continue to be a dominant theme with Dragonair and Altaria taking the lead. In Ultra League, Feraligatr safe swap has proven to be the superior formula, often combined with Skeledirge or Talonflame in the back. Take a look for more Pokemon and team ideas!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:11:04 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Shadow Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[A batch of new Shadow Pokemon debut next week, including Shadow Groudon and Shadow Pidgeot! Groudon appears to be a slight downgrade as Precipice Blades hits hard but isn't quite as fast as Shadow Groudon would like. Not to mention, Groudon bows to the current top Ground type, Landorus!<br><br>Pidgeot is one of the sims' favorite heroes, and Shadow Pidgeot provides interesting new dynamics for this baiting bird. It seems to perform better with Aerial Ace over Feather Dance; lower bulk reduces the effectiveness of Feather Dance's Attack drops, and if you want to hit harder, you may as well hit harder! On the whole, Shadow Pidgeot is a sidegrade to the original and may work better depending on your playstyle.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/pidgeot_shadow/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ultra Premier Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Ultra Premier makes its long-awaited return in a few weeks! Old contenders like Empoleon and Gallade have new life, while new contenders like Feraligatr and Annihilape will add major twists to this fan favorite meta.<br><br>Without Giratina or Cresselia in the mix, Poliwrath becomes a major target. Look for Grass and Electric Pokemon like Venusaur, Ampharos, Galvantula, or Lanturn to keep it at bay. Electric in particular has anti-meta potential with the strong number of Water and Flying types available.<br><br>In the mix of them all, Dragon stands out as a defining type for the meta. Shadow Dragonite should remain the pick of choice while several underused options like Dragalge and Goodra could see increased play with the Aqua Tail buff. With Fairy and Steel options looking limited, double Dragon lines could come roaring back from the Ultra Premier of years past. Empoleon is not only one of the best Dragon partners, but also now one of the best Dragon counters with Steel Wing instead of Waterfall. Avoiding the aforementioned Poliwrath will be vital for its success. Good luck! ]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/premier/2500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:48:53 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Master League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Top performers for Master League have been updated with training data from the past month. Some of this data precedes the Aqua Tail buff, so Palkia may perform better than the numbers shown. Zygarde/Solgaleo appear to remain top contenders, but the Origin Formes of Dialga and Palkia have proven highly effective after their debut.<br><br>Spring Cup also continues this week, so be on the lookout for a top performers update there as well!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com//train/analysis/all/10000/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Incineroar Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Incineroar is getting not one but two powerful attacks this weekend during Community Day—Blast Burn as an exclusive attack, and Darkest Lariat as a regular attack. Which do you want for your Incineroar? Maybe both!<br><br>Incineroar can generate energy quickly with either Snarl or Double Kick, and both Charged Attacks provide immense damage output. Blaze Kick can come in clutch, but Blast Burn isn't that much further to reach. Look to evolve multiple for each league if you want flexibility with your movesets.<br><br>Both attacks are major improvements for Incineroar, although it likely won't rise beyond a spice or themed cup pick with Water types drowning the open metas. Look to make the most of Incineroar in Ultra League, where its combats popular picks like Giratina and Cresselia. Enjoy your Community Day!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/incineroar/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 01:16:08 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Spring Cup Training Added</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Spring Cup is now available in the Train feature. Use it to practice your lineups or test new Pokemon! Pending sufficient training data, keep an eye out for Spring Cup training analysis next week.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:24:54 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers Update</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Top performers have been updated with an initial look at training analysis for the new meta! Feraligatr is the biggest new kid on the block, and it's been chomping at the bit for a meaningful move update. With Shadow Claw, it's now well on its way to solidifying itself in the meta. Shadow and non-Shadow Feraligatr combine to be top 5 in usage, and their performances have been similar with Shadow slightly edging out non-Shadow. Ice Beam appears to be the secondary move of choice (not enough data was recorded for Crunch).<br><br>With the rise of Feraligatr, Mandibuzz and Guzzlord demonstrated potential thanks to their Shadow Claw resistance. Guzzlord has been an early favorite so far, also resisting Lanturn and Charjabug. Dragon types as a whole have performed well have made a mark on this early meta, with the majority of top teams featuring Dragon leads. The meta is young and there are many opportunities for it to adapt especially as the tournament scene develops.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 15:39:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ceruledge and Armarouge Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[This family of fan-favorite Fire types debuts in eggs this coming event. In PvP, they're glass cannon Incinerate users that are viable to play, but they're a step down from Pokemon like Skeledirge or Talonflame.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/ceruledge/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 01:46:47 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Updated for World of Wonders</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The website is updated for the new season, World of Wonders! This update includes the new attack changes, and rankings for Electric Cup and Spring Cup.<br><br>The main metas should stay familiar overall. World of Wonders makes some Pokemon more viable than ever before, including Shadow Claw Feraligatr, Steel Wing Empoleon, and Psycho Cut Gallade. Some Dragon types are even stronger, too, with Dragonair, Goodra, and Hakamo-o all receiving buffs.<br><br>Enjoy the new season and good luck with your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:07:18 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>World of Wonders Rankings Preview</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[A preview version of the site is now available for next season, World of Wonders! This version includes updated attacks and movesets to prepare for next season's battles. Note that some move changes are speculative until the numbers can be confirmed when the new season launches at 1pm PST on Friday. Until then, happy studying!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/world-of-wonders/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 17:35:47 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Catch Cup Rankings, Great League Giratina</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted rankings for Great League Catch Cup as well as updated the Little Catch Cup rankings. Both of these use weightings based on usage data to help inform the scoring. Thanks, GO Battle Log!<br><br>In addition, a few legendaries have been introduced to Great League with the latest timed research, including Giratina's Origin forme. It isn't a meta-altering monster like its cousin, but it's still a strong corebreaker with anti-meta potential with resistances to Counter and elemental types. It will require trading to obtain, so make good use of your special trades at meetups and events!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/catch/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:07:24 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Little Catch Cup Rankings Updated</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Catch Cup is live, and Little Catch Cup appears to allow all Pokemon at 500 CP or below - including Shuckle and Smeargle. I've updated the rankings with all Pokemon, though note some Pokemon may not be obtainable such as certain Shadows or Legendaries. More so than ever, Little Catch Cup will emphasize which trainers are willing to invest significant resources into the cup's top picks. It's an opportunity to flaunt some fun catches if you have them, but otherwise, regular Catch Cup is still available.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/littlecatch/500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dialga Origin and Palkia Origin Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The Origin formes of Dialga and Palkia are debuting this weekend! Which should you prioritize for Master League?<br><br>Dialga has long been the meta defining Pokemon for Master League. Its Origin forme has a tradeoff in stats, slightly lower Attack but decently higher Defense and overall more stat product. In addition, Origin Dialga boasts Roar of Time, which is identical to Draco Meteor without the Attack debuff. Altogether, Origin Dialga is a slight improvement over Master League's biggest menace. The head to head matchup is about dead even. The biggest knock against Origin Dialga is that it loses Charged Move ties against its counterpart.<br><br>Palkia isn't meta defining like Dialga, however Origin Palkia is a significant upgrade over regular Palkia. It has both higher Attack and Defense stats, and while Spacial Rend doesn't hit as hard as Draco Meteor, it's a more flexible and accessible nuke. Palkia itself has significant opportunity in the current Master League meta where Landorus, Kyogre, and Ho-oh are popular picks, so its Origin forme should come out swinging.<br><br>If you have already built a Dialga, I recommend focusing on Origin Palkia since it's a more significant upgrade and it will add more depth to your Master League roster. If by chance you haven't built a Dialga yet, I would dedicate your efforts there so you can field Master League's most central Pokemon.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/palkia_origin/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Enamorus Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Enamorus has finally received stats and moves, and it looks like an aggressive pick in Master League and even Ultra League. This Fairy/Flying type is a glass cannon, but got access to Fairy Wind and Fly for rapid attacks. Its secondary moves include Dazzling Gleam (underwhelming but necessary to hit Dialga) and Grass Knot. Some might find Togekiss to be more reliable, but with that said, Enamorus brings more depth to Master League's Fairy roster and an energy oriented playstyle.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/enamorus_incarnate/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:38:52 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>
