<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Evolution Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Vigoroth is the theme of this season's themed cups, and it's back and better than ever in Evolution Cup. Primeape now joins the fray to keep Vigoroth in check, and Charjabug with Volt Switch should also be a key player. Evolution Cup lacks Steel and Fairy options, so expect Dragon types to run rampant in the early meta. Togetic and Metang may prove to be vital anti-meta picks to answer them! This is still Vigoroth's cup through and through, so I'd recommend it as a starting point for any meta or anti-meta team building.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/evolution/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:12:05 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisui Cup Updates</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated Hisui Cup resources to match the rule description on the Pokemon GO blog. The blog previously stated that Hisui Cup would include all Pokemon in the Pokemon Legends: Arceus Pokedex, but this information turned out to be incorrect and these Pokemon aren't eligible for Hisui Cup. Thanks for the patience on these updates!<br><br>Hisui Cup training is also now available with preset teams based on early usage data. Good luck in your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/hisui/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 21:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers Update</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated the Great League top performers with the past week of training data including Annihilape. This highly anticipated Pokemon has taken a strong, early position in the meta is already featured on both the top individual and team lists. It seems to fit a wide variety of teams, although it's commonly paired with a Steel type like Skarmory or Bastiodon which can cover its weaknesses to Fairy or Flying.<br><br>As the meta adjusts, other top performing Pokemon include Trevenant, Gligar, Charjabug, and Cresselia who could have opportunities. Each does well against Annihilape and a meta that is still oriented around Lanturn and other Water types. Good luck in the next week of battles and hopefully this list can provide inspiration!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:43:27 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sandsear Storm Landorus and Grassroot Tournament Updates</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Therian Landorus has arrived with its signature move, Sandsear Storm, and it's a major upgrade for Master League! Sandsear Storm may not be as strong as Superpower, but it makes Landorus more consistent and gives it much needed artificial bulk. Sandsear Storm + Stone Edge provides coveted Ground + Rock coverage, enabling Landorus to hit targets like Solgaleo and Metagross more effectively than before. If you're a Master League enthusiast, this is one you don't want to miss!<br><br>Catching up on the tournament side, I have updated data posted for all of the Battle Frontier formats and Devon Corp's new Sovereign Cup. Thanks for your patience on these and thanks to the respective teams for helping put these together!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/landorus_therian/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Revavroom and New Shadow Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The upcoming Rocket event features Revavroom's debut alongside multiple new Shadows. Revavroom is underwhelming, but several new Shadows will be great pick-ups for future themed cups, including Hisui Cup!<br><br>Toxicroak is the latest Shadow Counter user and is generally an upgrade, with its heavy Fast Attack pressure, an accessible Charged Attack in Mud Bomb, and new coverage from Shadow Ball. Froslass is comparable to Venusaur in both power and pacing, and is also worth having on hand as a PvP staple. Other notable picks include Empoleon and Crustle, both of which sport strong Fast Attack pressure and have themed cup potential. Have fun and don't forget to remove Frustration!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/toxicroak_shadow/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:32:58 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Annihilape Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Annihilape has debuted in Pokemon GO with just about all the moves it could hope for! While it will have to wait for its signature move, Rage Fist, Annihilape arrives with significant PvP potential. It's viable in all three leagues, having the most play in Great and Ultra League. The key ingredient for Annihilape's success is its Ghost/Fighting typing, which gives it superiority over most other Counter users, especially Vigoroth and Medicham. Offensively, it has access to Counter and Shadow Ball, plus Ice Punch, Night Slash, or Close Combat.<br><br>There are no type combinations which resist all of Fighting, Ice, and Ghost, making Annihilape a strong generalist with few true walls. However, it does lack stat product and pacing, so it shouldn't prove as dominant as Medicham was in its heyday. Buddy up with your Primeape and good luck battling!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/annihilape/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 20:33:28 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisui Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisui Cup returns for the Season of Timeless Travels, but this time it includes the full Pokemon Legends: Arceus Pokedex! This adds a wealth of new picks on top of those from the Sinnoh region, including Lickitung, Gligar, Umbreon, Whiscash, and Walrein.<br><br>Compared to Sinnoh Cup, Whiscash should replace Gastrodon as the top "mudboy" and Lucario may see significantly less play with the inclusion of Shadow Machamp. Sparse Electric and Grass options could make Water types like Mantine and Whiscash fairly safe, and even with strong Ground types in the mix, don't count Bastiodon out of the running. Cresselia should play a key role in protecting it. Good luck preparing and battling!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/hisui/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 23:32:18 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisuian Typhlosion Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisuian Typhlosion debuts during a raid day event this coming Sunday! It's a Fire/Ghost type like Skeledirge, with an interesting mix of Charged Attacks including Shadow Ball, Wild Charge, Overheat, and Fire Punch. Ultimately it falls short with Hex or Ember as its Fast Attack options, plus its significantly lower bulk. Even if it eventually gets Blast Burn, Hisuian Typhlosion will be waiting for a Fast Attack upgrade.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/typhlosion_hisuian/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:07:15 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fantasy Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Fantasy Cup returns in a few weeks, this time in Great League! This cup includes Dragon, Steel, and Fairy types with no bans. At first glance, Registeel + Azumarill and Galarian Stunfisk + Azumarill are the cores to look out for with few corebreakers between them. Overall, Fantasy Cup will likely be a concentrated meta which has an emphasis on mirror matchups. Prepare your sword and shield accordingly!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/fantasy/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 21:28:07 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Added Frenzy Plant Decidueye</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[During Community Day on January 6th, Decidueye will debut with the exclusive move, Frenzy Plant, alongside its signature move, Spirit Shackle. Frenzy Plant will be enough to make Decidueye playable, but it will generally fall behind Trevenant in viability. It does have some advantages with its Grass oriented attacks, which make it better against Normal types and bulky Water types.<br><br>Presently, Spirit Shackle has low enough power that resisted Frenzy Plants are still better. If Spirit Shackle remains as is, Brave Bird is likely to be preferred as the secondary move instead. Time permitting, I'll be looking to post a brief article for Decidueye Community Day soon!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/decidueye/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 22:57:09 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Top Performers Updated for All Leagues</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[All three leagues return today, and I've updated the top performers page with data from the past several weeks of training. In Great League, Shadow Dragonair was the star of the show as a corebreaker to popular picks like Lanturn and Talonflame, while Skarmory dropped in performance. Will the meta developments from Play Pokemon tournaments carry over to GO Battle League? If so, expect more Charjabug, Lickitung, and Poliwrath to take the field.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 16:30:53 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Remix Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Great League Remix will be making a return in January! The banlist allows some powerful new picks to slip through the cracks, including Skarmory, Vigoroth, and Swampert. Only a handful of Steel types are in play, so similar to Retro Cup, there is room for Dragon and Ice types to thrive. Happy holidays and happy studying!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/remix/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:57:43 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ultra League Top Performers Updated</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Ultra League top performers have been updated with early training battle results. Poliwrath is the biggest topic of the new Ultra League, and it's having all of its expected success as an individual performer and on teams. Fire and Water are duking it out among top Pokemon, while Ultra League staples like Giratina and Cresselia continue to remain strong option. More data to come later in the season!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:12:47 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cetitan Rankings, Battle Logic Tweaks</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Cetoddle and Cetitan debut soon! These pure Ice types are comparable to Avalugg with high HP instead of Defense, and an overall lower stat product. They're unlikely to see competitive use but are plenty playable and worth holding onto for the future.<br><br>In the latest update, I've also tweaked the simulations to address Skarmory's move usage, particularly Brave Bird against bulky targets like Toxapex or Giratina. Skarmory will now prefer Sky Attack against these opponents, slightly improving its matchups and rankings.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/cetitan/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:56:35 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Retro Cup Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted top performers from a small sample of Retro Cup training battles and updated the Retro Cup rankings with weightings based on the past week of usage. Top performing teams include fewer Dragons and double-Dragons than I was expecting, and instead highlight Lanturn, Froslass, Jellicent, and bulky Normal types as potential team-building glue. Your mileage may vary.<br><br>High Lanturn, Altaria, and Froslass usage shed light on anti-meta opportunities in the rankings, including Pokemon like Abomasnow or Trevenant. Dragon types will continue to reign supreme in Retro Cup thanks to the absence of resistances, so choose your dragons wisely. Enjoy your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/retro/1500/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 23:43:49 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Rankings Updated</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated the Great League rankings with new weightings based on Pokemon usage in the first week of GO Battle League and usage in the Stuttgart Regional Tournament. This update places more emphasis on matchups against Pokemon like Lanturn, Azumarill, Skarmory, and Talonflame, and factors in a reduced usage of Grass and Dark types. As always, the rankings are just a starting point and a guideline for exploring the meta. Happy studying!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:59:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>
