<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Retro Cup Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted top performers from a small sample of Retro Cup training battles and updated the Retro Cup rankings with weightings based on the past week of usage. Top performing teams include fewer Dragons and double-Dragons than I was expecting, and instead highlight Lanturn, Froslass, Jellicent, and bulky Normal types as potential team-building glue. Your mileage may vary.<br><br>High Lanturn, Altaria, and Froslass usage shed light on anti-meta opportunities in the rankings, including Pokemon like Abomasnow or Trevenant. Dragon types will continue to reign supreme in Retro Cup thanks to the absence of resistances, so choose your dragons wisely. Enjoy your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/retro/1500/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 23:43:49 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Rankings Updated</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated the Great League rankings with new weightings based on Pokemon usage in the first week of GO Battle League and usage in the Stuttgart Regional Tournament. This update places more emphasis on matchups against Pokemon like Lanturn, Azumarill, Skarmory, and Talonflame, and factors in a reduced usage of Grass and Dark types. As always, the rankings are just a starting point and a guideline for exploring the meta. Happy studying!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:59:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Little Holiday Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Holiday Cup will be going fun sized in the Little Cup later this month. At the time of writing, Little Holiday Cup allows all Normal, Grass, Electric, Flying, Ghost, and Ice-type Pokemon at 500 CP or under. With no explicit bans, this would include Smeargle, which has yet to be eligible in a Little Cup format. Smeargle boasts a strong set of potential moves including Lock-On, Incinerate, Flying Press, V-Create, Sacred Sword, and more. This combined with its stat product should make it the dominant Pokemon if it is indeed allowed.<br><br>Beyond Smeargle, several Great League Pokemon such as Vigoroth and Alolan Marowak should make the jump to compete with Little Cup staples like Ducklett, Vulpix, Cottonee, and Litwick. Check out the rankings for more details!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/holiday/500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 22:45:44 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers Update</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Training Analysis has been updated with an early look at the Great League meta! The meta is still developing, and so far some of the obvious suspects top the charts including Lanturn and Skarmory. Talonflame neither overperformed nor underperformed, perhaps thanks to a surge in Lanturn and a developing Dragon anti-meta.<br><br>One big surprise is a plummet in both Sableye usage and performance. Its key target, Medicham, has been nerfed this season, coupled with a buff to Azumarill has spelled trouble for Sableye in the early goings.<br><br>Thanks for your hard practice and good luck through the start of the season!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Holiday Cup Rankings Added</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Rankings for the Great League Holiday Cup are now available! Vigoroth should prove to be even more dominant than before, and Talonflame, Lanturn, and Skarmory will continue their Great League tango here. Some new picks also enter the mix including Skeledirge, Charjabug, and Arctibax to serve as potential corebreakers. Study up before the weather outside gets frightful and stay tuned for Little Holiday Cup rankings next week!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/holiday/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 01:18:26 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Retro Cup Training Added</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Retro Cup training is now available to practice your teams! In addition, I've updated Great League training teams from early usage so far this season. Keep an eye out for a top performers update later next week breaking down the best performing Pokemon and teams in training so far. Good luck!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:48:51 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Updated for Season of Timeless Travels!</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The website is updated with the move changes for Season of Timeless Travels! Rankings, battle simulations, and the team builder now include the latest changes for this season. Retro Cup rankings are also now available, and Holiday Cup rankings will be coming shortly. You can expect a top performer update on the Training Analysis page after the first week of the season.<br><br>For this season, I've included two entries for Lanturn in the Great League rankings—one with Spark and one with Water Gun. Lanturn is the only Pokemon to be featured this way given its importance in the metagame, but I'll be considering how to expand this for the future.<br><br>Good luck in your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 20:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Added Hisuian Starters</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The Hisuian starter Pokemon are now available on the site, with Hisuian Samurott making its debut this Sunday! Note that these Pokemon do not have their Community Day exclusive moves available via Elite TM at this time. Hisuian Samurott will need to wait for Hydro Cannon to see much viability, and even then it's unlikely to surpass Greninja.<br><br>With this update, I've also fixed an issue where navigating directly to Multi-Battle would show results against all Pokemon instead of just the meta Pokemon.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/battle/multi/2500/all/samurott_hisuian/11/0-2-1/2-1/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 14:59:22 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Custom Moves to Preview New Season Updates</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[If you're looking to get a peek at next season's updates, I've added duplicates of the moves which are receiving changes so you can use them in the simulations. Some of these values are speculative since energy values won't be known until the season begins on Friday. A full site update will come then!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Season of Timeless Travels Announced</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The latest season and move updates have been announced! There is a lot to explore with nerfs to Psychic, buffs for Fire types, and wide move distributions for Trailblaze, Scald, Fly, and more. Not all of the move update numbers are known, so PvPoke will be updated for the new season after it begins on Friday, December 1st. See you then!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pokemongolive.com/post/go-battle-league-timeless-travels?hl=en</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:19:54 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Top Performers Updated for All Leagues</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[With just over a week in the season to go, I've updated the top performers lists for all three leagues. Check them out if you need some Pokemon or team ideas to cross the finish line! This will likely be my last update for the season, so catch you on December 1st for the new season updates. Good luck!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:31:40 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Catch Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Catch Cup rankings are now available! These rankings include most Great League Pokemon and are scored against the most used Pokemon in Catch Cup so far, including Clodsire, Quagsire, and Gligar. Special thanks to GOBattleLog for the usage data!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/catch/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 14:22:28 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ultra League Top Performers Updated</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Ultra League top performers have been updated with the past month of training data. Golisopod has continued to prove its part in the meta, and top teams are showing variety with Cresselia and Steelix as common anchors in the back. Take a look!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/2500/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:56:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Update 1.31.0 - RSS News Feed</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Site updates will now appear in a news feed on the homepage! I've previously posted these updates to Twitter, but as Twitter has become less accessible, I've been looking to make them available on the website itself. Subscribe with any RSS reader to stay updated on new rankings, top performer teams, and other site updates!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 15:33:09 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

		<item>
			<title>Mega Garchomp Added</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Mega Garchomp has been added to the main site! It boasts incredible stats, but lives in Rayquaza's shadow, and has tough moveset choices to make. Happy raiding!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/battle/multi/10000/custom/garchomp_mega/11/0-2-5/2-1/mastermega/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 9 Nov 2023 14:48:47 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers Update</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Coming at you with a mid-week top performer update featuring Clodsire! Mud Shot has an early lead over Poison Sting, but overall, multiple movesets look viable. Dewgong and Jellicent stand to gain if Clodsire hangs around (and Regi doesn't).]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 8 Nov 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

	</channel>
</rss>
