<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Fantasy Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Fantasy Cup (Great League Edition) returns in a few weeks for Dragon, Fairy, and Steel types to clash. This format has few changes from its run earlier this year, so teams from January should work just as well now. <br><br>Steel Wing and Shadow Empoleon are the biggest additions, resisting all moves from Azumarill and putting up a fight against Dragons and Galarian Stunfisk. Tapu Fini now has Nature's Madness as well, closing the gap between it and Azumarill and making ABB teams with both more potent. Lastly, Thunder Punch is arguably a better coverage move for Lucario than Blaze Kick, but both are viable options.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/fantasy/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:14:35 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The first training analysis of the season highlights Water Gun Lanturn, Quagsire, and Goodra as new elements to the meta. While this season doesn't have too many changes, some familiar faces are bringing new tricks. Fire types like Skeledirge and Typhlosion are also standing surprisingly strong against the Water types, and old favorites like Umbreon and Sableye appear to have a chance for a comeback.<br><br>Among the top performing teams, a Normal type such as Lickitung or Vigoroth seems to be the common glue holding these teams together. Both Pokemon are flexible and favor neutral play. At the same time, Fast Attack pressure teams with Bastiodon, Victreebel, Wigglytuff, Dragonair, and similar picks are also standing the test of time against the early season. Best of luck the rest of the week!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Ranking Updates</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[With NAIC behind us, I've brushed up the Great League rankings and meta group based on early usage so far. I've also adjusted a few recommended movesets—Cresselia is now back to Moonblast and Talonflame features a double Flying moveset that has been prominent in tournament play. As always, the rankings are just a starting point. Good luck in your upcoming battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Goomy Community Day Guide</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Goodra has been on the outside looking in on the Great League meta. Will Thunder Punch help it punch a ticket to competitive success? This guide covers IV's to look for and the pros and cons to Goodra's multiple movesets. Good luck this weekend!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/community-day/24-06-goomy/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:18:59 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Custom Ranking Fixes</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated the custom rankings tool with some fixes and features that significantly speed up the time it takes to generate results. Under the "Advanced" settings, there's a new option that excludes low-performing Pokemon (Pokemon which have an overall score of less than 70 in the open league rankings). Depending on the cup, this can reduce the number of simulations required by up to half. The tool is much faster in general now, especially for "open" style formats.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:33:53 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Goodra Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Goodra is getting Thunder Punch for its Community Day, expanding its coverage options. In terms of overall performance, Thunder Punch appears on par with Power Whip or Draco Meteor for Great League, while it has fewer targets in Ultra League. Which moveset you choose may depend on your team and personal preferences. Make sure to grab Thunder Punch Goodra this weekend just in case!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/goodra/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:13:32 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Season of Shared Skies Updates</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The main website is now updated with the move changes for Season of Shared Skies. This includes attack value changes and movepool additions. Good luck preparing and enjoy your battles!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 14:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Next Season Preview</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Next season's PvP updates have been revealed, and the site is now updated with preview rankings which include the changes. Most notably, Spark and Scald nerfs should dial back Lanturn and Whiscash in Great League. The move updates don't have much immediate impact alone, but these small but important changes could open the door for meta shifts as teams adjust.<br><br>Note that next season's move updates will go live on June 3rd, after the weekend's Play! Pokemon events.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/shared-skies/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 19:09:19 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Update 1.31.9</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[The site has been updated with a few new features and fixes:<br><br>- In single battles, you can select "1 turn switch" under a Pokemon's options to simulate the battle with 1 turn of delay for that Pokemon. The optimal move timing guide also reflects the 1 turn delay.<br>- Matchup differences in Matrix Battle are now color coded with the gradient to reflect which differences are hard wins, soft wins, etc.<br>- Fixed an issue where battle time was being calculated incorrectly for mirror matchups.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:14:31 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Ultra Beast Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Three new Ultra Beasts are coming, including Stakataka, Blacephalon, and Naganadel, which can evolve from Poipole. Unfortunately, none of them are noteworthy for PvP at this time. Blacephalon and Naganadel suffer from incredibly low stat product while Stakataka doesn't have the moves to stand out. Keep a lookout for more Ultra Beasts in the future!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/blacephalon/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:07:24 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Catch Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Rankings are now available for Catch Cup (Great League Edition). These rankings implement usage data from the first few days to highlight which Pokemon may have an advantage in the current meta. For example, Carbink has strong matchups against popular Pokemon like Mandibuzz, Mantine, Skeledirge, and Charjabug. As always, Catch Cup is restricted to the best Pokemon available to you, so your mileage may vary. Good luck the rest of the season!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/catch/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 20:26:45 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tsareena Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[It's Bounsweet Community Day this weekend, and Tsareena will receive a new move, High Jump Kick. This Fighting-type nuke has a 10% chance to lower your Defense by 4 stages, so it comes with a big risk. Tsareena seems to be best with Triple Axel and High Jump Kick. However, it struggles to stand out among stronger Grass types like Abomasnow or Chesnaught, who benefit from STAB. I'd recommend obtaining High Jump Kick Tsareena just in case!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/tsareena/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 13:22:22 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tapu Fini Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Tapu Fini is the last to receive Nature's Madness, and it's a notable buff for the Water/Fairy Pokemon! Nature's Madness isn't as powerful as Moonblast, but the lower energy cost and the guaranteed Defense drop make Tapu Fini more flexible and dynamic. It's worth grabbing Tapu Fini if you don't have one already, and Nature's Madness is worthy of an Elite TM.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/tapu_fini/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:48:19 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Rankings Performance Comparison</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've added a small new feature that lets you compare the "Performance" details of two Pokemon in the rankings. Click the "Compare" button to select a Pokemon, and then you'll be able to compare their performance charts and numbers for each ranking category. You can use this to compare two similar Pokemon or two forms (such as Shadow vs non-Shadow).]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:31:30 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Updated Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Top performers have been updated on the Training Analysis page with top performing Pokemon and teams for all three leagues from the past month of training battles. Check them out if you need some team ideas!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Remix Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[This season's Great League Remix bans several of the league's most infamous Pokemon, while others such as Gligar and Annihilape slip through the cracks. Similar to previous Remixes, Dragon, Dark, and Ice-type Pokemon stand to gain from banning the strongest Steels and Fairies. Empoleon, Steelix, Carbink, and Alolan Ninetales look ready to step up to the plate but face their fair share of challenges as well.<br><br>One of the biggest questions is which Electric types will fill the gap left by Lanturn and Charjabug? Magnezone has seen recent tournament success while Dedenne could potentially thrive in an anti-meta role thanks to its Fairy typing. Good luck preparing!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/remix/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:25:41 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>
