<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>Top Performers Updated</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Top Performers page for all leagues with training data from the past month. Data is limited for Ultra League and Master League, so take those listings with a healthy dose of salt. In Great League, Ghost types continue to be a common element for top performing teams, typically paired with a Fighting-weak partner like Cradily, Bastiodon, or Furret. Take a look for some Pokemon and team ideas, and good luck as the season continues! ]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:37:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dudunsparce Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Dudunsparce has arrived as a more Attack-weighted alternative to Dunsparce. This difference generally puts it at a disadvantage and reduces its play in neutral matchups. With the exact same moveset as its pre-evolution, Dudunsparce lacks any distinguishing factors. However, it can reach Ultra League!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/dudunsparce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rankings and Editor Scores</title><description><![CDATA[The site's rankings now include "Editor Scores", personal ratings and notes for some individual Pokemon. These scores aim to highlight core meta Pokemon, correct ratings for Pokemon which may be under represented in the simulations, and provide additional commentary outside of the simulated results.<br><br>Editor scores will be expanded and updated across the three main leagues as the season progresses. I hope the results make the rankings more helpful!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fantasy Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Fantasy Cup returns in a few weeks, and the kingdom looks like it'll have quite a few shakeups. With significant changes to Dragons and a number of powerful new Fairies, Steel types like Galarian Stunfisk, Empoleon, and Corviknight look to have a major advantage. There are plenty of Pokemon with mixed movesets in the running, such as Turtonator, Togekiss, or Forretress. Azumarill is likely to remain core meta but faces more challenges this time around.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/fantasy/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadows and Team Builder Tweaks</title><description><![CDATA[A batch of new Shadows are releasing soon! All of them are promising PvP picks, including Altaria, Zweilous, and Claydol. Of the bunch, Zweilous and Hydreigon have the speed to take the most advantage of the Shadow boost.<br><br>In addition, I've made a few updates to the Team Builder to improve usability and results. Shadow Pokemon are now enabled by default, and follow the emphasis on meta picks so that the results highlight meta relevant Shadows. Suggested Alternatives also now use a more curated threats list, removing similar Pokemon from the list. For example, Shadow and non-Shadow versions of the same Pokemon won't be included in the six threats used to generated the Suggested Alternatives results.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 18:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flabébé Community Day Guide for PvP</title><description><![CDATA[Florges is learning Chilling Water this coming Community Day! It will be a strong contender in all three leagues, so don't miss out. Here's a deep dive on IV's to look for and Florges's prospects this season. Have fun!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/community-day/25-09-flabebe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 01:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florges Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[We're getting another amazing Community Day for PvP this month with Chilling Water Florges! It's viable in every league, but stands out most in Ultra and Master League. Chilling Water improves Florges's coverage and combines with Fairy Wind's pacing to artificially boost Florges's bulk. In Great League, Florges may play second fiddle to other Fairy options like Dedenne, Togekiss, or Azumarill, but it's still a strong contender. This one is a can't miss!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/florges/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:56:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mega Master League Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Mega Master League is returning after a long hiatus. If it actually sticks this time, it shouldn't be too unfamiliar territory. Primal Groudon, Primal Kyogre, and Mega Rayquaza remain top choices alongside Mega Gyarados. Groudon and Gyarados are both even stronger with the changes to Dragon Tail and Dragon Breath, respectively. However, the nerf to Breaking Swipe brings Rayquaza more in line with other Dragon options.<br><br>Team building for Mega Master League may essentially come down to picking one of the four above, or a counter pick like Mega Gardevoir or Mega Scizor. Non-Mega picks are also limited in viability, with only the biggest names like Crowned Zacian, Crowned Zamazenta, Origin Palkia, and Origin Dialga standing up to the top Megas.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/mega/10000/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated Top Performers with a first look at Great League this season. As the meta continues to evolve, top performing teams highlight several newcomers, including Corviknight, Empoleon, and Togekiss, and a strengthening role for Stunfisk against them. Ghost is another successful group in the early running, often paired with Cradily or Gastrodon. While Primeape usage is trending up, its performance has plummeted. Clodsire is another struggling member of the old guard.<br><br>The meta is changing fast with lots of new picks to explore, so time will tell which will come out on top in the early season!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 20:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Season of Transformation Updates</title><description><![CDATA[The site has been updated for Season of Transformation! There are some differences between the final move values and the ones speculated on the preview site, so the rankings have been updated to reflect these. Look forward to Summer Cup rankings soon and further updates as we roll into the new season. Have fun!<br><br>]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookidee Community Day Guide for PvP</title><description><![CDATA[Corviknight has hovered on the edge of the PvP meta, but may finally have its chance to swoop in. It's getting a crucial speed buff with its exclusive attack, Air Cutter. Will it be enough to push Corviknight into core relevance? Let's look ahead to the move updates next season to get a bird's-eye view on Corviknight's prospects.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/articles/community-day/25-08-rookidee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:55:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[With one last week in the season, I've updated Great League top performers with the past few weeks of training data. Shadow Giratina makes a peek in this data but it's still too early to draw any conclusions. Cradily has a firm stake in the top performing teams. Water and Ghost continue to be prominent typings, although an increase in Dark (specifically, Galarian Moltres) doesn't bode well for some of the Ghosts. Good luck the rest of the season and see you for the next one! Expect some major shakeups!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dondozo Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Dondozo is a pure Water type which is making its debut in raids. Its high base HP gives it a stat product similar to Lapras, but its Fast Attack options in Water Gun and Waterfall currently limit its effectiveness. It has future potential, so look to catch one for your collection!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/dondozo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:55:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Season Preview</title><description><![CDATA[I've posted a preview version of the site which includes moves, movesets, and rankings with the announced changes. Since many energy values can't be confirmed until the new season begins, this preview is highly speculative. It should serve as a potential reference, but avoid investing in any Pokemon until the move updates are confirmed. Happy studying!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/new-season-2026/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternatus Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Eternatus makes its massive debut, and it's going to take massive dedication to power it up. For Master League players, Eternatus can firmly hold its own among the legendary powerhouses. Its Poison subtyping is largely a footnote compared to its huge stat product and its powerful signature move, Dynamax Cannon. Like other Dragons, it will struggle against Zacian and Zamazenta, but it should have no trouble finding play especially as we look forward to next season.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>