<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>Catch Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Anything goes in Catch Cup where you can battle with any Great League Pokemon you've caught this season. This should play like open Great League for the most part, but the availability of some staple picks (especially Shadows) may affect the metagame. Shadow Jumpluff, for example, has had a recent dominating stretch but may be benched for this cup.<br><br>A few thrifty and popular picks include Furret, Feraligatr, Skeledirge, and Thievul. Good luck during this GO Battle Week!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/catch/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:49:23 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Urshifu Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Kubfu will be able to evolve into Urshifu next week with the option of two styles, Rapid Strike (Fighting/Water) and Single Strike (Fighting/Dark). While Urshifu can fit into the lower leagues, it's best suited for Master League - although as we'll get to below, it may only have a short window in the metagame.<br><br>Single Strike Urshifu is currently the better of the two with access to Sucker Punch, while Rapid Strike has nerfed Counter. Single Strike's Dark typing is also more appealing than Water in the current Master League meta. Urshifu's stats and attacks fall short of top tier legendaries like Origin Palkia, Black/White Kyurem, and Necrozma, so it's likely to fill more of an anti-meta or corebreaking role.<br><br>However, Urshifu has to contend with the upcoming release of Crowned Zacian and Zamazenta, which look to shatter Master League as we know it. Both will significantly reduce its viability, ultimately making Urshifu a poor long term investment for PvP.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/urshifu_single_strike/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:30:10 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Retro Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Apologies for the delay! Initial rankings and resources are now posted for Retro Cup. Similar to the Remix we just saw, Retro Cup tosses out the biggest answers to Ghost and Dragon, leaving these offensive types to wreak havoc. Expect plenty of double-Ghost or double-Dragon lines in this format! Bulky Pokemon like Jumpluff and Lapras should provide anchors for other team building schemes.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/retro/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kingambit and New Shadow Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Kingambit and new Shadow Pokemon make their upcoming debuts. Kingambit is the final evolution of Bisharp and a Dark/Steel glass cannon. It's a spice pick for the lower leagues, but keep an eye on Master League and Master Premier where it has some corebreaker potential against Steel + Fairy teams. It will need to wait for its signature move or potential move updates to reach its full potential.<br><br>Shadow Malamar commands the most attention of the new batch. As a core meta Pokemon already, Shadow Malamar makes for an exciting alternative. It's well-suited for the Shadow role thanks to its Fast Attack pressure and spammy Charged Attacks. Aurorus is another interesting choice that will likely see play in themed cups. In Master League, Shadow Dialga carries big name recognition but is outclassed by the Origin form. Note that Shadow Dialga doesn't have the strict IV requirements of its non-Shadow counterpart - it will generally always deal and take 5 Dragon Breath damage in the mirror matchup.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/10000/overall/kingambit/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:32:12 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Team Builder and Bug Fixes</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've made the following site updates and fixes:<br><br>- Fixed an issue where using the "Custom Threats" option of the Team Builder would sometimes return unexpected results for suggested alternatives.<br>- Fixed an issue where the "Custom Alternatives" option of the Team Builder would use default movesets instead of the movesets provided.<br>- Fixed an issue where closing the Pokebox feature would prevent it from opening again.<br>- Play! Pokemon Championship format is now listed in the Team Builder and Multi-Battle.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Top Performers Updated</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Training Analysis has been updated for all three leagues with data collected so far this season. Check out the top performers for some Pokemon or team ideas against the current meta. Good luck with your practice and keep it up as we head into the second half of the season!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 21:58:23 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Appletun and Flapple Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Appletun and Flapple debut as Grass/Dragon types with differing stats and movesets. Neither is competitive in their current state (they're comparable to Alolan Exeggutor), but Appletun has the most potential. It packs decent stat product with room to improve its movepool with attacks like Dragon Tail, Sucker Punch, Trailblaze, and an eventual signature move.<br><br>Applin also has unreleased alternative evolutions, Dipplin and Hydrapple. Hold onto them in case of future updates!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/appletun/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Remix Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Great League Remix returns next month, this time banning the 20 most used Pokemon from the current season. The bans include staples like Azumarill and Clodsire, plus newcomers like Cradily and Lapras.<br><br>Remix should shape up to be a wide open meta with a deep roster of remaining Pokemon. Among them are Great League powerhouses like Claydol, Diggersby, and Galarian Corsola. Some strong but underused Pokemon should also come to the forefront, such as Jellicent and Grumpig.<br><br>As usual for Great League Remix, Ghost and Dragon appear to be strong offensive types with the top Dark, Steel, and Fairy options banned. Galarian Corsola, Dusclops, and Dusknoir may be able to take advantage of this, but watch for Furret, Guzzlord, Umbreon, and others to step up. Meanwhile, Dragons might be more limited here than in past remixes since there are several strong Steel options present.<br><br>The most notable of these is Tinkaton, which only recently debuted. Not only does it pack Steel typing, it's likely to fill Azumarill's spot as the dominant Fairy. Its biggest challenge is accessibility, so time will tell if there are enough Tinkaton in circulation to truly shape the meta.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/remix/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 17:53:26 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tinkaton Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Tinkaton makes its debut with smashing potential for PvP! As a bulky Fairy/Steel type, it packs a whopping 11 resistances. Its Charged Attack options are underwhelming, but Fairy Wind lets it make the most of them. Altogether, Tinkaton should see immediate play in Great League and become a contender in Ultra League as well.<br><br>Tinkaton's Charged Attack options include Play Rough, Heavy Slam, Flash Cannon, and Bulldoze. Play Rough is a clear choice, balancing energy and power. Steel is a limited offensive typing, so neither Heavy Slam nor Flash Cannon are immediately obvious choices. Between the two, Heavy Slam is much more accessible at 50 energy. Bulldoze is Tinkaton's weakest attack, but may have some play. It provides meager coverage against Fire, Poison and other Steel types (such as the mirror matchup), and some trainers might like its chaotic debuff potential. Bulldoze is also Tinkaton's lowest energy attack at 45 energy.<br><br>Note that Tinkaton will be exclusive to 7km eggs and paid Timed Research encounters during its debut event. It will be available in 10km eggs after the event.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/tinkaton/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:27:34 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Eldegoss and Upper Hand Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Eldegoss has debuted in Pokemon GO. It's a pure Grass type with decent bulk, but its pure Grass movepool limits its potential for now.<br><br>Heracross, Hariyama, and Scraggy are receiving the new attack Upper Hand in a raid day this weekend. None of these Pokemon are currently viable, but Upper Hand looks like convincing option even with attacks like Close Combat and Superpower in the mix. Upper Hand clocks in at 40 energy and has a 30% chance to reduce the target's Defense by one stage. This makes it one of the fastest moves for these Pokemon, and it has great damage output without a self-inflicted debuff. Both Heracross and Hariyama would need a lot of help in the future to become meta relevant, but something to keep an eye on for the future.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/eldegoss/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:36:50 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Spring Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Spring Cup arrives next week, featuring Water, Grass, and Poison types. This rotation includes bans to Jumpluff, Roserade, and Toxapex. These bans plus drastic move updates should help this Spring Cup turn over a new leaf. Since the typings are limited, still anticipate a narrow meta.<br><br>Ferrothorn, Lapras, and Galarian Weezing are three standout Pokemon that may form the core meta. They have few corebreakers between them. Golisopod and Araquanid help break things up, but must watch for Cradily, which has seen rising play in Open Great League. There are other Steel options to keep an eye on, such as Empoleon, Mawile with your choice of Fire Fang or Astonish, or the regional Klefki. However, note that Tinkaton will debut in the second half of the rotation.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/spring/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Paldean Tauros Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Regional forms of Tauros will be debuting in raids. Each is a Fighting type with below average stat product but interesting moves, including Double Kick and Trailblaze. Blaze Breed and Aqua Breed Tauros can be found in the Eastern and Western hemispheres respectively, while Combat Breed Tauros is exclusive to the Iberian Peninsula.<br><br>Overall, the Paldean Tauros forms have middling PvP performance with some themed cup potential. Aqua Breed Tauros has the most potential as a spammy alternative to Poliwrath with the newly buffed Aqua Jet. The Combat and Blaze forms are usable but don't compare to stronger Fighting types.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/tauros_aqua/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:48:38 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated the Great League top performers with training analysis from the season so far! The meta is still changing, especially in the wake of new Play! Pokemon tournament results, so keep an eye out for new meta shakers in GO Battle League.<br><br>So far, top individual performers include Dazzling Gleam Sableye, Cradily, and Lapras. Both Cradily and Lapras have found their way onto a number of top performing teams as well, commonly paired with Annihilape checks like Clodsire, Talonflame, Skeledirge, or Grumpig. Speaking of Clodsire, it's a member of the old guard that's still holding on in this new meta and featured on many top teams. It's a strong check to Morpeko's swarming presence, although it's facing rising competition from Claydol for its role. Claydol recently saw notable success in the Stockholm regional tournament running Rock Tomb + Ice Beam.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Master Premier Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Master Premier returns in a few weeks, and its top meta Pokemon received some love in the recent move update. Most notably, Florges now packs Attack-boosting Grass coverage in Trailblaze. Some trainers previously opted for Petal Blizzard for the same coverage, but Trailblaze is a clear upgrade that elevates this top meta Pokemon to even stronger levels. Meanwhile, Golisopod should have a larger role in the core meta with the changes to Aqua Jet. Not to be overlooked, Hex Gholdengo is back as one of the best closers in the format.<br><br>Pokemon that may be vital tools against the top meta include Metagross and Skeledirge. Skeledirge entirely walls Florges, and Torch Song now provides momentum that it can carry over into the next matchup. Some may still opt for Disarming Voice given the presence of Dragons.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/premier/10000/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 15:20:04 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bug Fixes and UI Updates</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've made a few updates and fixes to the website including the following:<br><br>- Pokemon group selection and Matrix Battle results now display the Pokemon in a numbered list. This should help identify Pokemon among a large group of similar ones.<br><br>- The "@legacy" search term no longer includes Pokemon that know Frustration or Return.<br><br>- Fixed an issue where the "Performance" radar chart would appear in error on ranking subcategory pages where that data isn't available.<br><br>- Fixed a minor sim issue where Pokemon would sometimes throw an inefficient Charged Attack right before fainting.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 01:35:44 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>
