<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>New Shadow Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[A batch of new Shadow Pokemon are debuting, including the Kalos starters! Greninja is the most exciting of the bunch, with the fastest Hydro Cannon in the game and now also the strongest. Night Slash, which lacks in raw damage, will benefit from the extra power as well. All in all, Shadow Greninja should be a general upgrade over the normal version. Time will tell if it has just enough bulk to compete! ]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/greninja_shadow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:22:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Sorry for the delay! Rankings are now available for Master and Ultra Premier Cup. Both should tread familiar territory. Master Premier welcomes Cetitan and Dragon Breath Tyranitar into the fold, while Gholdengo looks to surf to new heights. Ice types must contend with Metagross, which is more powerful than ever.<br><br>Ultra Premier only removes a handful of meta players like Virizion, Cobalion, and Giratina, so Ultra League players should feel right at home here. Some underused picks have a chance to shine, such as Forretress, Oranguru, or Ampharos.<br><br>Good luck in your battles!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/premier/10000/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kilowattrel Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Kilowattrel is an Electric/Flying type comparable to Zapdos in most respects, but also worse in most respects. It's even glassier and its cheapest attack, Aerial Ace, is a considerable downgrade from Drill Peck. If you don't have access to a Great League Zapdos, Kilowattrel can fill in for that spice role. Look to grab one just in case!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/kilowattrel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Retro Cup returns next week, and it should look similar to its previous runs. Without Dark, Fairy, or Steel types, Dragon and Psychic are the dominating offensive types. Anticipate teams to double up on these unresisted attackers. Ghost is another potent type, but is countered by key Normal types, including Oranguru, Furret, and Lickilicky. An anti-meta type to look into is Bug, with Pokemon like Golisopod, Crustle, and Araquanid providing counterplay to Psychic (Oranguru in particular).]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/retro/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blacepholon Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Blacepholon is lighting up the new year with its exclusive move, Mind Blown. At 35 energy and 90 base power, this Fire-type Attack is one of the most efficient in the game, but comes with a steep 4 stage debuff to Blacepholon's Defense. Blacepholon already an extreme glass cannon - even glassier than Haunter - so it has to hope that back-to-back attacks are enough to KO. It's a spicy addition to the Fire/Ghost spectrum, so enjoy it's short-lived time on the field!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/blacephalon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coalossal and Sunshine Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Sunshine Cup will kick off in the new year, featuring Normal, Grass, Fire, and Ground types. New among them will be Coalossal, a bulky Rock/Fire Pokemon comparable to Magcargo. It lacks Incinerate but sports even more bulk. While it it's unlikely to contend much in the open leagues, it does have a place in themed cups like this one. Happy holidays and new year's!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/sunshine/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:43:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Holiday Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[A lot has changed since Holiday Cup: Great League Edition last saw the GBL rotation in 2023. Normal types like Lickilicky, Dunsparce, and Furret stand out as versatile centerpieces, which must seek to avoid Annihilape and the format's various Steel types. Protecting them are dangerous Fire types including Talonflame and Skeledirge. There yet remain ghosts of Christmas past, as Sableye and Alolan Marowak are in strong contention. This cup is likely to be top-heavy, but there is a deep roster for corebreaking opportunities.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/holiday/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scroll Cup Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Scroll Cup is returning, featuring Fighting, Water, and Dark-type Pokemon. This should remain a small meta with Gastrodon, Azumarill, and Dark/Flying types taking center stage. That said, recent changes give more viability to a few members of the cup. These include Kingdra, Sableye, Murkrow, Zweilous, Guzzlord, Jellicent, and more. Good luck in the early season!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/scroll/1500/overall</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 21:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precious Paths Update</title><description><![CDATA[The site is now updated for the latest season, Precious Paths! If you've checked the preview over the past week, the final attack values match what was expected. Keep an eye out for ranking updates as the season progresses and as the new meta game takes shape, with updated editor's scores and meta group selections. Enjoy the new season!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toucannon Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Toucannon is receiving Beak Blast this Community Day, and it's a big improvement for the plucky bird. Beak Blast has comparable numbers to Brave Bird, but instead of debuffing the attacker, it provides a guaranteed Attack drop on the opponent. This gives Toucannon similar prospects to Pidgeot, Dodrio, and other Pokemon with mono-Flying offenses, if perhaps a bit better. These Pokemon don't typically see much competitive action but are viable for GO Battle League and themed cup play.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/toucannon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precious Paths Preview Page</title><description><![CDATA[A preview version of the site is now available for Precious Paths, including all move updates for next season! Note that some of these are speculative as energy values won't be known until the season starts. Take a look and happy studying!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/precious-paths/rankings/all/1500/overall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morgrem and Grimmsnarl Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Thanks for your patience on the latest updates! The Impidimp family has now been added to the rankings. These Dark/Fairy types sport high Attack stats and solid movesets to compete in Great and Ultra League. Morgrem has slightly higher stat product for Great League while Grimmsnarl is the only one that can reach Ultra League. Both have corebreaking potential, excelling against Ghost types and rival Dark types.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/grimmsnarl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spidops Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Spidops is on a mission and it's getting the green light! Bug types usually need a lot of help, but Spidops has a few things going for it—good bulk plus a solid moveset with Lunge, Rock Tomb, and its choice of Shadow Claw or Bug Bite. Its closest comparisons are Golisopod and Forretress. Though it lacks their better typings, it still looks to be competitive in Open Great League. It may succeed more in themed cups where it will have fewer direct threats.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/spidops/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top Performers Updated</title><description><![CDATA[Top Performers are now updated for Great League and Ultra League with the past month of training data. In Great League, Forretress and Scizor are gaining a stronger foothold, while in Ultra League, Chilling Water Florges is beginning to break out into the meta. Take a look for some team ideas and good luck during this GO Battle Weekend!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:31:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Shadow Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Two new Shadow Pokemon debut in raids during part one of the Halloween Event - Phantum and Yamask. Their evolutions, Trevenant and Cofagrigus, aren't currently top Ghost-type options, but interesting additions to the Shadow roster. Shadow Trevenant relishes the reduced energy cost of Seed Bomb and looks to be largely on par with the normal version. Meanwhile, Shadow Cofagrigus is at bit of a disadvantage with its slower moveset—not quite a nail in the coffin, but it'll have to wait for a faster Charged Attack option. Return looks intriguing for normal Cofagrigus and trainers brave enough to try it.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/trevenant_shadow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>