<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">

	<channel><item><title>Great League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[I've updated the Great League top performers with a sampling of teams and Pokemon from recent training. While this sample is small, it highlights some successful experimentation with Pokemon like Pangoro, Dragalge, and Galarian Moltres. Good luck in your battles and keep up the practice!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toedscruel Rankings</title><description><![CDATA[Toedscruel debuts as a Grass/Ground type with the same bulk as its toxic lookalike. With a solid moveset, it can pair Mud Slap with Seed Bomb, Earth Power, Wrap, or Acid Spray. Wrap in particular gives it similar play to Gastrodon, plus a guaranteed Defense drop to bolster its Fast Attack pressure.<br><br>Unlike Gastrodon, Toedscruel's typing gives it more weaknesses to juggle. Its triple resistance to Electric and single resistance to Ground are offset by a double weakness to Ice and single weaknesses to Fire, Flying, and Bug. This profile limits Toedscruel as a Mud Slapper generalist, so it must seek out top targets like Dedenne, Marowak, or Clodsire to counter. Even with Seed Bomb, it struggles against Water types, which often pack Ice coverage. It should see play in themed cups and perhaps it'll find an anti-meta role too!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/toedscruel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aegislash Update</title><description><![CDATA[After a crazy debut, the dust has settled on Aegislash! The simulations have now been updated to implement Aegislash's forme change mechanic. Aegislash begins in its bulky Shield forme and transforms into its glass cannon Sword form before it launches any Charged Attack. It reverts to its Shield forme when it uses a Protect Shield or swaps out.<br><br>While in Shield forme, Aegislash's Fast Attack is overridden to have 0 base power and generate 6 energy per use. While in Blade forme, Aegislash's effective level is reduced in Great and Ultra League in an attempt to keep its new CP under the league caps.<br><br>Aegislash is most effective when it minimizes its time in Blade forme. Generally, Aegislash should seek to build up to 100 energy before throwing. It should also absorb hits while in Shield forme to save shields for its Blade forme. On the flip side, opponents should avoid throwing energy into Aegislash's Shield forme and wait until it's vulnerable in its Blade forme. Fast Attack pressure is key to countering Aegislash, which is especially vulnerable to poor Charged Attack timing.<br><br>I'll continue to watch for more details on Aegislash's mechanics and provide QOL updates to help analyze this crazy new Pokemon. Thanks for your patience!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/aegislash_shield/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title/><description><![CDATA[Quaquaval will be receiving Aqua Step as a regular addition to its movepool, and Hydro Cannon as an exclusive move during its upcoming Community Day! Aqua Step boosts its Attack by one stage, but it's overshadowed by the sheer power of Hydro Cannon.<br><br>While Quaquaval has great Charged Attack options, it wishes for the days of peak Wing Attack. It won't see much play until it finds better energy generation in a future update. In the meantime, grab some for the collection and have fun!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/quaquaval/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:27:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Team Builder Update</title><description><![CDATA[The Team Builder now prioritizes showing meta relevant Pokemon in its threats and suggested alternatives. This should help provide better suggestions and threats which you are more likely to encounter (sorry, Fletchinder).You can disable this feature in the advanced settings if you want to explore more spice picks or find off-meta corebreakers. Have fun!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/team-builder/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Master League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[Master League is returning, and it's undergoing a monumental shakeup with the arrival of the Crowned forms of Zacian and Zamazenta. Top performing teams highlight Crowned Zacian + Origin Palkia as one of the most common and successful cores. Kyurem (both Black and White) still appears to remain a major player, but Dusk Mane Necrozma is on a downturn, dropping significantly in team rating and usage.<br><br>"If you can't beat 'em, join 'em" has never been more true for Master League. However, a few Pokemon are holding on for an anti-meta role. Rhyperior and Landorus still land among the top performing teams despite their weaknesses, and Dawn Wings Necrozma stands out with solid matchups against the core meta. With Solgaleo now more widely available, time will tell if it has a role to play as well.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/10000/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 17:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Update to Default IV's</title><description><![CDATA[The rankings and default simulations don't use rank 1 IV's, but lower ranked IV combinations which are intended to represent an average version of the Pokemon. The default IV's were previously around ranks 150-300 depending on the Pokemon and followed rules which were difficult to explain. In response to survey feedback, I've tweaked the default IV's with the following changes.<br><br>- Default IV's now use the best ranked IV combination with an IV floor of 4. Default IV's are now around ranks 50-150, but still keep that distinct Attack weight for the sake of comparison.<br>- In cases where the above doesn't reach the CP limit, Pokemon will use the best ranked Lucky IV combination (floor of 12).<br>- Overall, default IV's should better represent competitive play.<br><br>You may notice some slight shifts in the rankings due to these changes, as the default IV change may allow some Pokemon to reach breakpoints or bulkpoints which the previous IV's didn't.]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:30:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultra League Top Performers</title><description><![CDATA[While training data for Ultra League has only a small sample, I've posted the results so far and updated the default training teams to reflect the new Bellibolt meta. This smiley chunkster demands counterplay from picks like Gastrodon, Virizion, and Guzzlord. Zygarde Complete also looks like the complete package if you have the option. Best of luck in your practice and thanks for any training you contribute!]]></description><link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/all/2500/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisuian Zoroark Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisuian Zoroark is a unique Ghost/Normal typing, which makes it the only Pokemon to resist both Ghost and Fighting attacks. However, as a Haunter-like glass cannon, Hisuian Zoroark can't take much damage of any kind! Its movepool gives it some play as a spice pick, with access to Shadow Claw, Foul Play, and Shadow Ball for a mix of Fast Attack pressure, speed, and nuke potential. Be prepared for some quick battles!<br><br>]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/1500/overall/zoroark_hisuian/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 16:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hisui Cup Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Hisui Cup will be returning in a few weeks, and it should play a bit different this time around but with some usual suspects crowding the scene. Drapion, Gliscor, and Gastrodon form a hard triangle against which corebreakers like Drifblim, Vespiquen, and Empoleon may find play. Add Spiritomb into the mix, and you have a subset of flexible Pokemon which only sport one weakness each. As usual, themed cups are about finding hidden opportunities in a limited meta, so we'll see which gems are out there!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/hisui/1500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 23:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>PvPoke.com Feedback Survey</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've posted a feedback survey to help gather information on which areas of the website you'd like to see improve and which new features you'd most be interested in. I'll be using this feedback to address any changes requested by the community and plan site updates over the next few months. Thanks in advance and thanks for your support!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://forms.gle/ZPUr1Vz45AUXpbis7</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:41:31 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great League Top Performers</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've updated Great League training analysis from the first leg of the season, including top Pokemon and teams which players have practiced.<br><br>The data highlights opportunities for Pokemon like Shadow Gligar, Shadow Typhlosion, and the Bug/Water types of Araquanid and Golisopod to make headway into the meta. Shadow Scizor and Dedenne are also putting up strong individual performances, backed by early tournament results.<br><br>A few curious patterns appear on top performing teams. Normal types such as DIggersby, Furret, and Dunsparce are a common successful element, paired with a Fire type like Talonflame or Shadow Typhlosion. This is a time of rapid change as the meta seeks to resolve itself, so your mileage may vary. Best of luck as we head further into the season!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/train/analysis/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 23:09:31 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kommo-o Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[This upcoming Community Day, Kommo-o will receive its signature move, Clanging Scales. As of now, Clanging Scales is the highest damage-per-energy attack in the game, with 120 base power at the cost of 45 energy and a 1-stage Defense drop. However, Kommo-o faces problems if it wants to put Clanging Scales into practice.<br><br>Kommo-o isn't quite a glass cannon, but has below average stat product. Energy generation with Dragon Tail can be cumbersome, so Kommo-o and similar Dragon types perform best with 35-energy attacks like Dragon Claw or Aqua Tail. If Kommo-o wants to use Clanging Scales, it must sacrifice either pacing or coverage. By dropping Dragon Claw, Kommo-o's impressive attacks are simply outpaced. By dropping Close Combat, Kommo-o loses the ability to hit back at Steel. Brick Break is a middle ground, but doesn't appear fast or strong enough to solve the problem.<br><br>Kommo-o seems to perform best in Ultra League where it has more bulk to work with and it can reach its powerful attacks more reliably. Despite Clanging Scales tipping the scales on attack power, Kommo-o may need to wait for better energy generation to actually make some noise in the metagame. That said, make sure to take advantage of the event to prepare one for your collection!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/all/2500/overall/kommo_o/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:07:32 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Performance Improvements</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[I've pushed various performance improvements including battle and interface optimizations:<br><br>- Battle simulations should be about 25% faster, with more noticeable improvement in bulk simulations (such as the Team Builder or Custom Rankings)<br>- The Pokemon Select dropdown now only displays Pokemon near the current selection rather than the full Pokedex.<br>- The above should help the "Add Pokemon" window on Team Builder or Matrix Battle appear immediately rather than after a delay.]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/#news</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 15:13:53 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Summer Cup (UL) Rankings</title>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[Summer Cup is returning, this time in Ultra League. It features prominent Water, Electric, and Grass types with a handful of Fire, Normal, and Bugs clawing for relevancy. As usual in these limited formats, Pokemon which can break the mold of their type typically prove the strongest. Here, this includes Cradily, Victreebel, Tentracruel, Lapras, Jellicent, and Golisopod. This cup may be resource demanding if you haven't built the requisite Pokemon yet, so now may be a good opportunity to expand your Ultra League roster. Good luck and enjoy the sun!]]>
			</description>
			<link>https://pvpoke.com/rankings/summer/2500/overall/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:12:51 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		

		<title>PvPoke</title>
		<link>https://pvpoke.com/</link>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Website updates for PvPoke.com and other news for Pokemon GO PvP.]]>
		</description>

	</channel>
</rss>